<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<products>
<product>
    <code>NAV111TR</code>
    <name>
        <value language="fr"></value>
        <value language="en">Norton™ AntiVirus 30-Day Trial</value>
    </name>
    <type>trial</type>
    <taxcode>GOODS</taxcode>
    <brand>Symantec</brand>
    <image>norton-anti-virus.png</image>
    <availability>
        <storevisible>true</storevisible>
        <notsoldseperately>false</notsoldseperately>
        <enabledate>2013-03-01T10:46:00-08:00</enabledate>
        <minorderqty>1</minorderqty>
        <availabilityrule>ALWAYS_AVAILABLE</availabilityrule>
        <orderlimit>0</orderlimit>
    </availability>
    <attributes>
        <attribute key="system_requirements">
            <value>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Operating Systems Supported&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft® Windows® XP (32-bit) Home/Professional/Tablet PC/Media Center (32-bit) with Service Pack 2 or later&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Windows Vista® (32-bit and 64-bit) Starter/Home Basic/Home Premium/Business/Ultimate with Service Pack 1 or later&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Windows 7 (32-bit and 64-bit) Starter/Home Basic/Home Premium/Professional/Ultimate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Windows 8 and Windows 8 Pro (32-bit and 64-bit)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum Hardware Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;300 MHz for Microsoft Windows XP, 1 GHz for Microsoft Windows Vista/Microsoft Windows 7/Windows 8&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;256 MB of RAM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;300 MB of available hard disk space&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CD-ROM or DVD drive (if not installing via electronic download)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Browser Support for Vulnerability Protection&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot; style=&quot;margin-bottom: 3px;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Internet Explorer® 7.0 or higher (32-bit only)&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mozilla® Firefox® (32-bit only)&lt;sup&gt;1,2&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="longDesc">
            <value>&lt;p&gt;Basic antivirus protection that stops viruses and spyware, so you can safely go online and share.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Five patented layers of protection quickly and accurately detect and eliminate viruses and spyware.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lets you download and freely share without getting or passing on viruses.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protects your privacy and prevents your passwords and identity from being stolen when you surf the Web.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="features">
            <value>&lt;h3&gt;EXCLUSIVE&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norton Protection System&lt;/strong&gt; – Our 5 patented layers of protection detect and eliminate threats more quickly and accurately than other technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Browser Protection&lt;/strong&gt; – Proactively protects you by checking for and blocking online threats as your browser loads, to stop online threats before they can do damage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;IMPROVED&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SONAR Behavioral Protection &amp;amp; Live 24x7 Threat Monitoring&lt;/strong&gt; – Stays ahead of, detects and eliminates threats that haven’t been invented yet by watching your PC for suspicious activity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;NEW&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Threat-removal Layer&lt;/strong&gt; – Targets and eliminates hard-to-remove threats less sophisticated products often miss.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;EXCLUSIVE&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Insight&lt;/strong&gt; – Improves performance by identifying safe files and only scanning unknown files. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Download Insight 2.0 &lt;/strong&gt;– Protects you from dangerous applications before you install them by telling you if they are harmful or unstable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;NEW&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Always up-to-date Product Version&lt;/strong&gt; – Norton automatically sends you important product and feature updates throughout the year. The latest version installs without you needing to do anything.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FREE 24x7 Support &lt;/strong&gt;– Offers you expert help and answers by phone, live chat or online, whenever you need them.&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;EXCLUSIVE&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norton Management&lt;/strong&gt; – Cloud-based controls let you fix, update, renew and install Norton AntiVirus over the Internet with a few simple clicks. It brings together your available Norton protection for other devices, like your Mac® computer, smartphone or tablet, in one place.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;IMPROVED&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bandwidth Management 2.0 &lt;/strong&gt;– Automatically adjusts Norton data usage updates when you connect to 3G networks to avoid using up your monthly data allotment or causing overage fees.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vulnerability Protection &lt;/strong&gt;– Stops cybercriminals from using security holes (vulnerabilities) in applications to sneak threats onto your PC.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;EXCLUSIVE&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norton Pulse Updates &lt;/strong&gt;– Updates your protection every 5 to 15 minutes, without disrupting you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="benefits">
            <value>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Free Trial - Norton™ AntiVirus&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click on the button below to start downloading a  FREE 30-day trial of the full product with no obligation. See  additional installation instructions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h3 class=&quot;mod&quot;&gt;Benefits&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;mod&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Say goodbye to viruses&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It's okay to blink, because we never do – SONAR technology and live 24x7 Threat Monitoring watch over your PC for any suspicious behavior to quickly identify threats.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Download away – we scan the files you download and eliminate online threats that we find.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep clean your PC – our powerful Threat-Removal Layer targets and scrubs out aggressive, hard-to-remove infections that less sophisticated products often miss. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Harness global power – only Norton can bring you the ultra-fast Network Defense Layer to block a multitude of threats before they can even touch your PC.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protection from the future, available today – our exclusive reputation and behavior antivirus technology are so advanced that they can stop online threats that bad guys haven't even created yet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep out trespassers – Browser Protection blocks unsafe websites that secretly download software that can steal personal information or take over your PC.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shop, surf and visit social networks without worry&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It's easy to stumble into the wrong part of the web – we block &quot;phishing&quot; websites set up to trick you into leaking your passwords, credit card numbers or worse.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Facebook links are tempting – now you don't need to worry if a Facebook News Feed contains dangerous downloads or fraudulent links.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protects your identity by securely storing and automatically entering your user names and passwords.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Engineered to go unnoticed – because great protection doesn't get in your way or slow you down&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blazingly fast performance delivers fast browsing and file scanning.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intelligent detection and quiet background operation block threats and won’t overload you with pop-up warnings or restart requests.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;So smart, it scans and runs updates only when you’re not using your PC—with no need to reboot after updates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Everyone's talking cloud. And with our new Cloud-based Norton Management, it’s easy to stay in control&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lets you fix, update, renew or install Norton products on additional PCs without needing to track down the product key or install CD. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works from anywhere over the Internet with a few simple clicks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="shortDesc">
            <value language="en">Keep your computer safe from viruses and spyware with the industry’s most powerful protection.</value>
        </attribute>
    </attributes>
    <skus>
        <sku guid="F6C6ED90-1967-527E-E646-15944EFDE8E3">
            <code>NAV111TR</code>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true">
                <file>N360W.exe</file>
                <downloadexpiry>0</downloadexpiry>
                <downloadlimit>0</downloadlimit>
            </digitalasset>
        </sku>
    </skus>
    <seo>
        <url>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </url>
        <title>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </title>
        <keywords>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </keywords>
        <description>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </description>
    </seo>
</product>

<product>
    <code>TIBRAN111TR</code>
    <name>
        <value language="fr"></value>
        <value language="en">Rendezvous Software Trial</value>
    </name>
    <type>trial</type>
    <taxcode>GOODS</taxcode>
    <brand>Tibco</brand>
    <image>blank-box.png</image>
    <availability>
        <storevisible>true</storevisible>
        <notsoldseperately>false</notsoldseperately>
        <enabledate>2013-03-01T10:49:00-08:00</enabledate>
        <minorderqty>1</minorderqty>
        <availabilityrule>ALWAYS_AVAILABLE</availabilityrule>
        <orderlimit>0</orderlimit>
    </availability>
    <attributes>
        <attribute key="longDesc">
            <value>TIBCO Rendezvous® is the leading messaging product for real-time, multicast-based broad data distribution. It has been used by thousands of customers for more than a decade, and is the backbone for several of the largest mission-critical systems in production today.</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="features">
            <value>&lt;div style=&quot;width: 390px;&quot; class=&quot;column-main&quot;&gt;
							
								&lt;div class=&quot;intro-only&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;TIBCO Rendezvous® is the industry-leading – and most widely deployed – low latency messaging and data distribution solution on the market. Proven by thousands of organizations worldwide, Rendezvous high-performance messaging middleware supports applications ranging from market data distribution and trading to real-time control systems, supply chains, and transportation networks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;With Rendezvous' flexible and scalable information bus infrastructure, you can build event-driven applications that unlock value from big data while it's in motion and before it enters a database.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rendezvous supplies a bandwidth-efficient, flexible platform for global application infrastructure. Its APIs for Java, C, C++, C#, Perl, and COM let you develop robust event-driven applications using the full capabilities of high-performance multi-processor servers and advanced networks. And to ensure low-latency, you can embed the TIBCO Rendezvous In-Process Module directly into your applications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For extreme low-latency messaging performance, Rendezvous natively integrates with TIBCO FTL®, and with TIBCO Enterprise Message Service™ for JMS-compliant enterprise messaging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;spaced&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Increase Throughput and Data Distribution:&lt;/strong&gt; Optimize network utilization for peer-to-peer multicast-based messaging.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Easily Manage Quality of Service:&lt;/strong&gt; Choose delivery levels from reliable to certified.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Increase Efficiency and Simplify Configurations:&lt;/strong&gt; Implement dynamic, source-based routing with interest-driven forwarding across multiple messaging domains.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lower Administration Costs:&lt;/strong&gt; Use centralized daemon management and self-managing protocols.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Improve Performance and Flexibility:&lt;/strong&gt; Rely on user extensible types for messaging.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Centralize Management:&lt;/strong&gt; Monitor and manage daemons, subjects, and multicast groups remotely via a browser interface or Java API.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;							
															
															
															
															
						&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="benefits">
            <value>&lt;div id=&quot;featureAttributeDiv&quot;&gt;
																		
				&lt;p&gt;Messaging can be publish/subscribe or request/reply, point-to-point or multicast, synchronous or asynchronous, and delivered via the local-area network (LAN), wide-area network (WAN), or the internet;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Choice of qualities of service from lightweight informational messages to reliable and certified delivery;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Peer-to-peer multicast-based messaging for efficient network utilization and scalability;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TIBCO Rendezvous® In-Process Module that embeds Rendezvous capabilities directly into applications for ultra-low latency needs;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Point-to-point and Wide Area Network (WAN) messaging support via TCP and SSL;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dynamic, source-based routing with interest driven forwarding provides added efficiency and simplified configuration across multiple messaging domains.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;br&gt;
		
														&lt;/div&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="shortDesc">
            <value language="en">TIBCO Rendezvous® is the leading messaging product for real-time, multicast-based broad data distribution.</value>
        </attribute>
    </attributes>
    <skus>
        <sku guid="4F409582-5C61-38E7-B72C-CEAFC98B3EAA">
            <code>TIBRAN111TR</code>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true">
                <file>TIBEMS111TRW.exe</file>
                <downloadexpiry>0</downloadexpiry>
                <downloadlimit>0</downloadlimit>
            </digitalasset>
        </sku>
    </skus>
    <seo>
        <url>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </url>
        <title>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </title>
        <keywords>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </keywords>
        <description>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </description>
    </seo>
</product>

<product>
    <code>TIBAMB111</code>
    <name>
        <value language="fr"></value>
        <value language="en">ActiveMatrix BusinessWorks Trial</value>
    </name>
    <type>trial</type>
    <taxcode>GOODS</taxcode>
    <brand>Tibco</brand>
    <image>blank-box.png</image>
    <availability>
        <storevisible>true</storevisible>
        <notsoldseperately>false</notsoldseperately>
        <enabledate>2013-03-01T10:52:00-08:00</enabledate>
        <minorderqty>1</minorderqty>
        <availabilityrule>ALWAYS_AVAILABLE</availabilityrule>
        <orderlimit>0</orderlimit>
    </availability>
    <attributes>
        <attribute key="longDesc">
            <value>TIBCO ActiveMatrix BusinessWorks™ is TIBCO’s flagship SOA automation platform that enables users to develop new services, orchestrate business processes and integrate applications with little or no coding. TIBCO ActiveMatrix BusinessWorks Developer Edition offers a powerful development environment that comes loaded with a broad selection of palettes to develop BusinessWorks projects. Using BusinessWorks’ simple, yet powerful model-driven development approach, users can develop and debug new services, configure integration process flows, transform data formats without having to write any lines of code.</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="features">
            <value>&lt;div class=&quot;intro-only&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;TIBCO ActiveMatrix BusinessWorks™ is a robust and highly scalable platform that can be used to develop new services, automate business processes, and integrate applications – minimal code required.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Higher Productivity, Faster Results&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A unified, model-driven design environment (IDE) allows developers and administrators to rapidly create, orchestrate, and integrate highly modular services and flexible business applications. Everything they need to service- or event-enable processes, including protocols or transforming data from one system to another, is right at their fingertips.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Built to run natively with other ActiveMatrix products, this elastic platform can meet your immediate business needs and flex over time – allowing you to start small and add other capabilities to your service-oriented architecture (SOA) as new requirements arise. A wide array of plug-ins and adapters can also be used to yield greater speed and performance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Enterprise-Ready: Proven. Scalable. Reliable.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;As TIBCO's flagship, industry-leading platform, ActiveMatrix BusinessWorks is currently used by thousands of companies worldwide – most notably serving as the foundation for several of the largest mission-critical, service-oriented business applications in production today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Its performance, scalability, and reliability has been proven to support up to 1 billion messages per day – over 25,000 per second – with 99.999% or greater uptime. Organizations that have implemented SOA using this solution have achieved 30% to 60% greater productivity compared to alternative technologies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;spaced&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accelerate Time-to-Results:&lt;/strong&gt; Developers and administrators can build and change services, processes, and applications with little to no coding&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enhance Efficiency:&lt;/strong&gt; Expose existing applications as reusable services, assemble and orchestrate these services to create more flexible composite applications, and deploy and manage applications more efficiently&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lower Total Cost of Ownership:&lt;/strong&gt; Open standards and native web service supports higher production in less time using fewer resources&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expand Connectivity:&lt;/strong&gt; Adapters yield greater speed, performance, and results by accelerating the integration of any third-party application and technology&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Optimize Automation Levels:&lt;/strong&gt; Seamless transfer of data enterprise-wide enables transactions to be processed faster and accelerates business processes throughput&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Increase Reliability:&lt;/strong&gt; Services are deployed on a horizontally scalable, distributed enterprise service bus (ESB), minimizing risk of failure&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accelerate Recovery:&lt;/strong&gt; Advanced capabilities support flow control, dependency tracking, and the ability to automate self-healing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;							
															
															
															
															
															
															
						&lt;/p&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="benefits">
            <value>&lt;p&gt;Simple, yet powerful model-driven development paradigm that involves little or no coding for the fastest time to results;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Powerful connectivity lets users integrate any application on any platform using out-of-the box palettes and plug-ins such as SOAP, JMS, JDBC, File, HTTP, etc.;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shrink Total Cost of Ownership with enhanced developer productivity that enables you to focus on value-adding business logic instead of low-level automation;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Powerful Visual Debugger to test business processes and services.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot; http://www.tibco.com/products/automation/application-integration/activematrix-businessworks/default.jsp&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Learn more about TIBCO ActiveMatrix BusinessWorks™&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;br&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="shortDesc">
            <value language="en">TIBCO ActiveMatrix BusinessWorks™ is TIBCO’s flagship SOA automation platform that enables users to develop new services, orchestrate business processes and integrate applications with little or no coding.</value>
        </attribute>
    </attributes>
    <skus>
        <sku guid="A5EF937B-CC98-485A-A6FD-AFEB06683DE1">
            <code>TIBAMB111</code>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true">
                <file>TIBAMB111W.exe</file>
                <downloadexpiry>0</downloadexpiry>
                <downloadlimit>0</downloadlimit>
            </digitalasset>
        </sku>
    </skus>
    <seo>
        <url>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </url>
        <title>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </title>
        <keywords>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </keywords>
        <description>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </description>
    </seo>
</product>

<product>
    <code>TIBEMS111TR</code>
    <name>
        <value language="fr"></value>
        <value language="en">Enterprise Message Service Trial</value>
    </name>
    <type>trial</type>
    <taxcode>GOODS</taxcode>
    <brand>Tibco</brand>
    <image>blank-box.png</image>
    <availability>
        <storevisible>true</storevisible>
        <notsoldseperately>false</notsoldseperately>
        <enabledate>2013-03-01T10:54:00-08:00</enabledate>
        <minorderqty>1</minorderqty>
        <availabilityrule>ALWAYS_AVAILABLE</availabilityrule>
        <orderlimit>0</orderlimit>
    </availability>
    <attributes>
        <attribute key="features">
            <value>&lt;div class=&quot;intro-only&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Businesses have become increasingly dependent on the real-time flow of information. When it isn't available for decision-making, or when data is locked in databases, you can't execute, capture value from your critical information assets, or compete in the way you want, in the way that delights customers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;TIBCO Enterprise Message Service™ (EMS) is a standards-based messaging platform that brings together IT assets and communications technologies on a common high-performance messaging backbone. EMS scales horizontally to support real-time decision-making across the organization, to unlock data siloed in databases and applications, and to power business operations for fast, event-driven execution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;spaced&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reduce Cost, Complexity, and Time:&lt;/strong&gt; Integrate disparate systems using a common backbone that supports open standards, existing systems, and native support for a broad range of technologies for servers, desktops, and mobile devices including C, COBOL, Java EE, and .NET.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Secure Leading Performance, Scalability, and Reliability:&lt;/strong&gt; Leverage TIBCO's integrated suite of products for fast implementation of 21st Century architectures and increased development and operations productivity.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enable Access to Information On the Go:&lt;/strong&gt; Extend the high performance enterprise messaging backbone to web and mobile devices with TIBCO Web Messaging for TIBCO EMS.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Remove Single Points of Failure:&lt;/strong&gt; Integrate into a distributed and reliable architecture with load-balancing, routing, and fault tolerant configurations that can reliably deliver high-throughput messaging with 99.99% uptime.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deliver Secure Messaging:&lt;/strong&gt; Support security and administrative control including SSL for client-to-server and server-to-server connectivity and plug-in security for custom-built authentication (JAAS).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support Demanding Applications:&lt;/strong&gt; Support several protocols on the same platform and several quality of service levels – and supply broad messaging semantics and different messaging including externally managed XA-compliant transactions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;							
															
															
															
															
						&lt;/p&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="longDesc">
            <value>&lt;p&gt; 	       TIBCO Enterprise Message Service™ is a standards-based enterprise messaging platform that brings together different IT assets and communications technologies on a common real-time backbone and manages the real-time flow of information. TIBCO Enterprise Message Service reduces the cost, complexity and time required to integrate disparate systems by providing native support for multiple message protocols and technologies – including the Java Message Service (JMS) standard using with Java and J2EE, Microsoft .NET, TIBCO Rendezvous® and TIBCO SmartSockets™, and C and COBOL on the mainframe. It also delivers proven performance, scalability and reliability.
 
   &lt;/p&gt;,N/A</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="benefits">
            <value>&lt;div id=&quot;featureAttributeDiv&quot;&gt;
																		
				&lt;p&gt;Common messaging platform enabling the delivery of information using leading platforms, standards, and development technologies;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Multiple service protocols and qualities of service supported, providing one of the broadest sets of messaging semantics and options to optimize performance and service levels;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Distributed architecture avoids introduction of a single point of failure with support for load-balancing, routing, and fault tolerant configurations;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Administrative control to maintain a high performance and secure messaging solution, and supports security standards including SSL.
			&lt;br&gt;
		
														&lt;/div&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="shortDesc">
            <value language="en">TIBCO Enterprise Message Service™ is a standards-based enterprise messaging platform that brings together different IT assets and communications technologies on a common real-time backbone and manages the real-time flow of information.</value>
        </attribute>
    </attributes>
    <skus>
        <sku guid="B5A498F9-DB0F-399D-52AC-A8540E4709A5">
            <code>TIBEMS111TR</code>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true">
                <file>TIBEMS111.exe</file>
                <downloadexpiry>0</downloadexpiry>
                <downloadlimit>0</downloadlimit>
            </digitalasset>
        </sku>
    </skus>
    <seo>
        <url>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </url>
        <title>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </title>
        <keywords>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </keywords>
        <description>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </description>
    </seo>
</product>

<product>
    <code>NAV222TR</code>
    <name>
        <value language="fr"></value>
        <value language="en">Norton™ 360 30-Day Trial</value>
    </name>
    <type>trial</type>
    <taxcode>GOODS</taxcode>
    <brand>Symantec</brand>
    <image>norton-utilities.png</image>
    <availability>
        <storevisible>true</storevisible>
        <notsoldseperately>false</notsoldseperately>
        <enabledate>2013-03-01T11:41:00-08:00</enabledate>
        <minorderqty>1</minorderqty>
        <availabilityrule>ALWAYS_AVAILABLE</availabilityrule>
        <orderlimit>0</orderlimit>
    </availability>
    <attributes>
        <attribute key="system_requirements">
            <value>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Operating Systems Supported&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft® Windows® XP (32-bit) Home/Professional/Tablet PC/Media Center (32-bit) with Service Pack 2 or later&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Windows Vista® (32-bit and 64-bit) Starter/Home Basic/Home Premium/Business/Ultimate with Service Pack 1 or later&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Windows 7 (32-bit and 64-bit) Starter/Home Basic/Home Premium/Professional/Ultimate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Windows 8 and Windows 8 Pro (32-bit and 64-bit)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum Hardware Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;300 MHz for Microsoft Windows XP, 1 GHz for Microsoft Windows Vista/Microsoft Windows 7/Windows 8&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;256 MB of RAM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;300 MB of available hard disk space&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CD-ROM or DVD drive (if not installing via electronic download)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Browser Support for Phishing Protection, Safe Search, and Password Management&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot; style=&quot;margin-bottom: 3px;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Internet Explorer® 7.0 or higher (32-bit only)&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mozilla® Firefox® (32-bit only)&lt;sup&gt;1,2&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Google Chrome™&lt;sup&gt;1,2&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;span style=&quot;margin: 0 0 0 25px;&quot;&gt;&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;As made available by Symantec within your service period.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;margin: 0 0 0 25px;&quot;&gt;&lt;sup&gt;2&lt;/sup&gt;Supports current and the most recent previous 32-bit major releases.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Browser Support for Vulnerability Protection&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot; style=&quot;margin-bottom: 3px;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Internet Explorer® 7.0 or higher (32-bit only)&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mozilla® Firefox® (32-bit only)&lt;sup&gt;1,2&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;span style=&quot;margin: 0 0 0 25px;&quot;&gt;&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;As made available by Symantec within your service period.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;margin: 0 0 0 25px;&quot;&gt;&lt;sup&gt;2&lt;/sup&gt;Supports current and the most recent previous 32-bit major releases.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support for Antispam&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Outlook® 2002 or later&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Outlook Express 6.0 or later&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Windows Mail (spam filtering only)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="longDesc">
            <value>&lt;p&gt;Our ultimate Internet and antivirus protection for all you do online&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provides proactive protection, so you can do what you want online, knowing you’re protected.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ultra-fast Internet detection layer stops most threats before they can even reach your computer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Powerful threat-removal layer targets and eliminates even the hardest to remove infections. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="features">
            <value>&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;FEATURES&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our ultimate protection for your PC&lt;/strong&gt; – includes everything from Norton™ AntiVirus and Norton™ Internet Security with 2 GB of secured online storage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;EXCLUSIVE&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norton&lt;/strong&gt;™&lt;strong&gt; Protection System&lt;/strong&gt; – Our 5 patented layers of protection detect and eliminate threats more quickly and accurately than other technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Network Defense Layer Protection&lt;/strong&gt; – Stops online threats before they can reach your computer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;IMPROVED&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SONAR Behavioral Protection &amp;amp; Live 24x7 Threat Monitoring &lt;/strong&gt;– Stays ahead of, detects and eliminates threats that haven’t been invented yet by watching your PC for suspicious activity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;NEW&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Threat-removal Layer &lt;/strong&gt;– Targets and eliminates hard-to-remove threats less sophisticated products often miss.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;EXCLUSIVE&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norton&lt;/strong&gt;™ &lt;strong&gt;Management&lt;/strong&gt; – Cloud-based controls let you fix, update, renew and install Norton 360™ over the Internet with a few simple clicks. It brings together your available Norton™ protection for other devices, like your Mac® computer, smartphone or tablet, in one place.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norton&lt;/strong&gt;™&lt;strong&gt; Safe Web for Facebook &lt;/strong&gt;– Scans your Facebook News Feed for dangerous links, infected downloads and unsafe websites.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Automatic Backup &lt;/strong&gt;– Backs up your photos, music and other important files only when you’re not using your computer, so it won’t get in your way and you don’t have to remember to do it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PC Tuneup&lt;/strong&gt; – Fixes common computer problems, frees up memory, removes unnecessary files and cleans up your hard drive.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;NEW&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Always up-to-date Product Version&lt;/strong&gt; – Norton™ automatically sends you important product and feature updates throughout the year. The latest version installs without you needing to do anything.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FREE 24x7 Support&lt;/strong&gt; – Offers you expert help and answers by phone, live chat or online, whenever you need them. &lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;EXCLUSIVE&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Parental Controls Management&lt;/strong&gt; – Lets you access Norton™ Online Family through Norton 360™.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Antiphishing Technology&lt;/strong&gt; – Blocks fraudulent “phishing” websites set up by online scammers to steal your money, passwords, and identity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norton&lt;/strong&gt;™&lt;strong&gt; Identity Safe &lt;/strong&gt;– Remembers, secures and automatically enters your user names and passwords for you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;EXCLUSIVE&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Insight&lt;/strong&gt; – Improves performance by identifying safe files and only scanning unknown files.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norton&lt;/strong&gt;™&lt;strong&gt; Safe Web&lt;/strong&gt; – Proactively protects you while you surf the Web by warning of and blocking unsafe and fake websites right in your search results.&lt;sup&gt;2&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Browser Protection&lt;/strong&gt; – Proactively protects you by checking for and blocking online threats as your browser loads, to stop online threats before they can do damage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Web-Based Backup Access&lt;/strong&gt; – - Lets you download and share photos, videos and other files you’ve backed up online, anytime, anywhere via the cloud.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Download Insight 2.0&lt;/strong&gt; – Protects you from dangerous applications before you install them by telling you if they are harmful or unstable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vulnerability Protection&lt;/strong&gt; – Stops cybercriminals from using security holes (vulnerabilities) in applications to sneak threats onto your PC.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;IMPROVED&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bandwidth Management 2.0&lt;/strong&gt; – Automatically adjusts Norton™ data usage updates when you connect to 3G networks to avoid using up your monthly data allotment or causing overage fees.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;EXCLUSIVE&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norton&lt;/strong&gt;™&lt;strong&gt; Pulse Updates&lt;/strong&gt; – Updates your protection every 5 to 15 minutes, without disrupting you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="benefits">
            <value>&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Say goodbye to viruses&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It's okay to blink, because we never do – SONAR technology and live 24x7 Threat Monitoring watch over your PC for any suspicious behavior to quickly identify threats.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Download away – we scan the files you download and eliminate online threats that we find.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep clean your PC – our powerful Threat-Removal Layer targets and scrubs out aggressive, hard-to-remove infections that less sophisticated products often miss. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Harness global power – only Norton™ can bring you the ultra-fast Network Defense Layer to block a multitude of threats before they can even touch your PC.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protection from the future, available today – our exclusive reputation and behavior antivirus technology are so advanced that they can stop online threats that bad guys haven't even created yet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep out trespassers – Browser Protection blocks unsafe websites that secretly download software that can steal personal information or take over your PC.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Neutralize online identity thieves – it's the only way to shop, surf and visit social networks without worry&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It's easy to stumble into the wrong part of the web – we block &quot;phishing&quot; websites set up to trick you into leaking your passwords, credit card numbers or worse.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Facebook links are tempting – now you don't need to worry if a Facebook News Feed contains dangerous downloads or fraudulent links.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protects your identity by securely storing and automatically entering your user names and passwords.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Help keep kids safe from Internet dangers with Norton&lt;/strong&gt;™&lt;strong&gt; Online Family&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Easily connects you to Norton™ Online Family right from within your Norton™ Control Center.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lets you know what your kids are up to online by tracking which websites they visit, and allows you to block inappropriate sites.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keeps an eye on your kids’ social network activities and who they’re chatting with online, so you can spot potential dangers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Engineered to go unnoticed – because great protection doesn't get in your way or slow you down&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blazingly fast performance delivers fast browsing and file scanning.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intelligent detection and quiet background operation block threats and won’t overload you with pop-up warnings or restart requests.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;So smart, it scans and runs updates only when you’re not using your PC – with no need to reboot after updates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Everyone's talking cloud. And with our new Cloud-based Norton&lt;/strong&gt;™&lt;strong&gt; Management, it’s easy to stay in control&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lets you fix, update, renew or install Norton™ products on additional PCs without needing to track down the product key or install CD. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works from anywhere over the Internet with a few simple clicks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accidents happen. Hard drives fail. Coffee gets spilled. Make sure you always have a backup.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Automatic backup takes care of your photos, music, and other important files and backs them up to a disc, USB device, or online to one of our secure data centers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protects files you back up online with government-grade encryption.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lets you get up and running fast - Norton™ backup restores files with just a few clicks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PC need a pick me up? Keep it running fast and trouble-free with our exclusive clean up and tuneup features.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixes common problems that can slow down or cause your PC to crash or freeze.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gets rid of unnecessary files and optimizes your hard drive.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Frees up system memory.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="shortDesc">
            <value language="en">&lt;li&gt;Provides proactive protection, so you can do what you want online, knowing you’re protected.&lt;/li&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
    </attributes>
    <skus>
        <sku guid="CD305C3D-9AE2-8F88-A470-8348467548F5">
            <code>NAV222TR</code>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true">
                <file>software.exe</file>
                <downloadexpiry>0</downloadexpiry>
                <downloadlimit>0</downloadlimit>
            </digitalasset>
        </sku>
    </skus>
    <seo>
        <url>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </url>
        <title>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </title>
        <keywords>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </keywords>
        <description>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </description>
    </seo>
</product>

<product>
    <code>NAV333TR</code>
    <name>
        <value language="fr"></value>
        <value language="en">Norton™ Internet Security 30-Day Trial</value>
    </name>
    <type>trial</type>
    <taxcode>GOODS</taxcode>
    <brand>Symantec</brand>
    <image>norton-internet-security.png</image>
    <availability>
        <storevisible>true</storevisible>
        <notsoldseperately>false</notsoldseperately>
        <enabledate>2013-03-05T16:57:00-08:00</enabledate>
        <minorderqty>1</minorderqty>
        <availabilityrule>ALWAYS_AVAILABLE</availabilityrule>
        <orderlimit>0</orderlimit>
    </availability>
    <attributes>
        <attribute key="system_requirements">
            <value>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Operating Systems Supported&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft® Windows® XP (32-bit) Home/Professional/Tablet PC/Media Center (32-bit) with Service Pack 2 or later&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Windows Vista® (32-bit and 64-bit) Starter/Home Basic/Home Premium/Business/Ultimate with Service Pack 1 or later&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Windows 7 (32-bit and 64-bit) Starter/Home Basic/Home Premium/Professional/Ultimate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Windows 8 and Windows 8 Pro (32-bit and 64-bit)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum Hardware Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;300 MHz for Microsoft Windows XP, 1 GHz for Microsoft Windows Vista/Microsoft Windows 7/Windows 8&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;256 MB of RAM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;300 MB of available hard disk space&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CD-ROM or DVD drive (if not installing via electronic download)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Browser Support for Phishing Protection, Safe Search, and Password Management&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot; style=&quot;margin-bottom: 3px;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Internet Explorer® 7.0 or higher (32-bit only)&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mozilla® Firefox® (32-bit only)&lt;sup&gt;1,2&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Google Chrome™&lt;sup&gt;1,2&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;span style=&quot;margin: 0 0 0 25px;&quot;&gt;&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;As made available by Symantec within your service period.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;margin: 0 0 0 25px;&quot;&gt;&lt;sup&gt;2&lt;/sup&gt;Supports current and the most recent previous 32-bit major releases.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Browser Support for Vulnerability Protection&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot; style=&quot;margin-bottom: 3px;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Internet Explorer® 7.0 or higher (32-bit only)&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mozilla® Firefox® (32-bit only)&lt;sup&gt;1,2&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;span style=&quot;margin: 0 0 0 25px;&quot;&gt;&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;As made available by Symantec within your service period.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;margin: 0 0 0 25px;&quot;&gt;&lt;sup&gt;2&lt;/sup&gt;Supports current and the most recent previous 32-bit major releases.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support for Antispam&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Outlook® 2002 or later&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Outlook Express 6.0 or later&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Windows Mail (spam filtering only)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="features">
            <value>&lt;h3&gt;FEATURES&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advanced protection for your PC &lt;/strong&gt;– includes everything from Norton AntiVirus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;EXCLUSIVE&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norton Protection System&lt;/strong&gt; – Our 5 patented layers of protection detect and eliminate threats more quickly and accurately than other technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Network Defense Layer Protection&lt;/strong&gt; – Stops online threats before they can reach your computer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;IMPROVED&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SONAR Behavioral Protection &amp;amp; Live 24x7 Threat Monitoring&lt;/strong&gt; – Stays ahead of, detects and eliminates threats that haven’t been invented yet by watching your PC for suspicious activity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;NEW&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Threat-removal Layer&lt;/strong&gt; – Targets and eliminates hard-to-remove threats less sophisticated products often miss.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;EXCLUSIVE&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norton Management&lt;/strong&gt; – Cloud-based controls let you fix, update, renew and install Norton Internet Security over the Internet with a few simple clicks. It brings together your available Norton protection for other devices, like your Mac® computer, smartphone or tablet, in one place.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;NEW&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Always up-to-date Product Version&lt;/strong&gt; – Norton automatically sends you important product and feature updates throughout the year. The latest version installs without you needing to do anything.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norton Identity Safe&lt;/strong&gt; – Remembers, secures and automatically enters your user names and passwords for you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norton Safe Web for Facebook&lt;/strong&gt; – Scans your Facebook News Feed for dangerous links, infected downloads and unsafe websites.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;EXCLUSIVE&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Parental Controls Management&lt;/strong&gt; – Lets you access Norton Online Family through Norton Internet Security&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FREE 24x7 Support&lt;/strong&gt; – Offers you expert help and answers by phone, live chat, or online, whenever you need them.&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Antiphishing Technology &lt;/strong&gt;– Blocks fraudulent “phishing” websites set up by online scammers to steal your money, passwords and identity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;EXCLUSIVE&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Insight&lt;/strong&gt; – Improves performance by identifying safe files and only scanning unknown files.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norton Safe Web&lt;/strong&gt; – Proactively protects you while you surf the Web by warning of and blocking unsafe and fake websites right in your search results.&lt;sup&gt;2&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Browser Protection&lt;/strong&gt; – Proactively protects you by checking for and blocking online threats as your browser loads, to stop online threats before they can do damage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Download Insight 2.0&lt;/strong&gt; – Protects you from dangerous applications before you install them by telling you if they are harmful or unstable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vulnerability Protection&lt;/strong&gt; – Stops cybercriminals from using security holes (vulnerabilities) in applications to sneak threats onto your PC.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;IMPROVED&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bandwidth Management 2.0&lt;/strong&gt; – Automatically adjusts Norton data usage updates when you connect to 3G networks to avoid using up your monthly data allotment or causing overage fees.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;EXCLUSIVE&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norton Pulse Updates&lt;/strong&gt; – Updates your protection every 5 to 15 minutes, without disrupting you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="longDesc">
            <value>&lt;p&gt;Advanced Internet and antivirus protection for anywhere you go and anything you do online.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provides proactive protection, so you can do what you want online, knowing you’re protected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved SONAR technology and live 24x7 global threat monitoring stay ahead of emerging threats&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ultra-fast Internet detection layer stops most threats before they can even reach your computer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="benefits">
            <value>&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Say goodbye to viruses&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It's okay to blink, because we never do – SONAR technology and live 24x7 Threat Monitoring watch over your PC for any suspicious behavior to quickly identify threats.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Download away – we scan the files you download and eliminate online threats that we find.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep clean your PC – our powerful Threat-Removal Layer targets and scrubs out aggressive, hard-to-remove infections that less sophisticated products often miss. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Harness global power – only Norton can bring you the ultra-fast Network Defense Layer to block a multitude of threats before they can even touch your PC.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protection from the future, available today – our exclusive reputation and behavior antivirus technology are so advanced that they can stop online threats that bad guys haven't even created yet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep out trespassers – Browser Protection blocks unsafe websites that secretly download software that can steal personal information or take over your PC.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Neutralize online identity thieves – it's the only way to shop, surf and visit social networks without worry&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It's easy to stumble into the wrong part of the web – we block &quot;phishing&quot; websites set up to trick you into leaking your passwords, credit card numbers or worse.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Facebook links are tempting – now you don't need to worry if a Facebook News Feed contains dangerous downloads or fraudulent links.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protects your identity by securely storing and automatically entering your user names and passwords.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Help keep kids safe from Internet dangers with Norton Online Family&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Easily connects you to Norton Online Family right from within your Norton Control Center.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lets you know what your kids are up to online by tracking which websites they visit, and allows you to block inappropriate sites.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keeps an eye on your kids’ social network activities and who they’re chatting with online, so you can spot potential dangers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Engineered to go unnoticed – because great protection doesn't get in your way or slow you down&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blazingly fast performance delivers fast browsing and file scanning.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intelligent detection and quiet background operation block threats and won’t overload you with pop-up warnings or restart requests.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;So smart, it scans and runs updates only when you’re not using your PC – with no need to reboot after updates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Everyone's talking cloud. And with our new Cloud-based Norton Management, it’s easy to stay in control&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lets you fix, update, renew or install Norton products on additional PCs without needing to track down the product key or install CD. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works from anywhere over the Internet with a few simple clicks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="shortDesc">
            <value language="en">Advanced Internet and antivirus protection for anywhere you go and anything you do online.</value>
        </attribute>
    </attributes>
    <skus>
        <sku guid="E403C37A-040F-BB7E-E002-DAAD34088164">
            <code>NAV333TR</code>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true">
                <file>software.exe</file>
                <downloadexpiry>0</downloadexpiry>
                <downloadlimit>0</downloadlimit>
            </digitalasset>
        </sku>
    </skus>
    <seo>
        <url>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </url>
        <title>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </title>
        <keywords>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </keywords>
        <description>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </description>
    </seo>
</product>

<product>
    <code>TIBAMB11</code>
    <name>
        <value language="fr"></value>
        <value language="en">ActiveMatrix BusinessWorks</value>
    </name>
    <type>product</type>
    <taxcode>GOODS</taxcode>
    <brand>Tibco</brand>
    <image>blank-box.png</image>
    <availability>
        <storevisible>true</storevisible>
        <notsoldseperately>false</notsoldseperately>
        <enabledate>2013-03-01T09:46:00-08:00</enabledate>
        <minorderqty>1</minorderqty>
        <availabilityrule>ALWAYS_AVAILABLE</availabilityrule>
        <orderlimit>0</orderlimit>
    </availability>
    <attributes>
        <attribute key="longDesc">
            <value>&lt;p&gt;TIBCO ActiveMatrix BusinessWorks™ is TIBCO’s flagship SOA automation platform that enables users to develop new services, orchestrate business processes and integrate applications with little or no coding. TIBCO ActiveMatrix BusinessWorks Developer Edition offers a powerful development environment that comes loaded with a broad selection of palettes to develop BusinessWorks projects. Using BusinessWorks’ simple, yet powerful model-driven development approach, users can develop and debug new services, configure integration process flows, transform data formats without having to write any lines of code.&lt;/p&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="features">
            <value>&lt;div class=&quot;intro-only&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;TIBCO ActiveMatrix BusinessWorks™ is a robust and highly scalable platform that can be used to develop new services, automate business processes, and integrate applications – minimal code required.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Higher Productivity, Faster Results&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A unified, model-driven design environment (IDE) allows developers and administrators to rapidly create, orchestrate, and integrate highly modular services and flexible business applications. Everything they need to service- or event-enable processes, including protocols or transforming data from one system to another, is right at their fingertips.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Built to run natively with other ActiveMatrix products, this elastic platform can meet your immediate business needs and flex over time – allowing you to start small and add other capabilities to your service-oriented architecture (SOA) as new requirements arise. A wide array of plug-ins and adapters can also be used to yield greater speed and performance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Enterprise-Ready: Proven. Scalable. Reliable.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;As TIBCO's flagship, industry-leading platform, ActiveMatrix BusinessWorks is currently used by thousands of companies worldwide – most notably serving as the foundation for several of the largest mission-critical, service-oriented business applications in production today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Its performance, scalability, and reliability has been proven to support up to 1 billion messages per day – over 25,000 per second – with 99.999% or greater uptime. Organizations that have implemented SOA using this solution have achieved 30% to 60% greater productivity compared to alternative technologies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;spaced&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accelerate Time-to-Results:&lt;/strong&gt; Developers and administrators can build and change services, processes, and applications with little to no coding&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enhance Efficiency:&lt;/strong&gt; Expose existing applications as reusable services, assemble and orchestrate these services to create more flexible composite applications, and deploy and manage applications more efficiently&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lower Total Cost of Ownership:&lt;/strong&gt; Open standards and native web service supports higher production in less time using fewer resources&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expand Connectivity:&lt;/strong&gt; Adapters yield greater speed, performance, and results by accelerating the integration of any third-party application and technology&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Optimize Automation Levels:&lt;/strong&gt; Seamless transfer of data enterprise-wide enables transactions to be processed faster and accelerates business processes throughput&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Increase Reliability:&lt;/strong&gt; Services are deployed on a horizontally scalable, distributed enterprise service bus (ESB), minimizing risk of failure&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accelerate Recovery:&lt;/strong&gt; Advanced capabilities support flow control, dependency tracking, and the ability to automate self-healing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;							
															
															
															
															
															
															
						&lt;/p&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="benefits">
            <value>&lt;p&gt;Simple, yet powerful model-driven development paradigm that involves little or no coding for the fastest time to results;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Powerful connectivity lets users integrate any application on any platform using out-of-the box palettes and plug-ins such as SOAP, JMS, JDBC, File, HTTP, etc.;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shrink Total Cost of Ownership with enhanced developer productivity that enables you to focus on value-adding business logic instead of low-level automation;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Powerful Visual Debugger to test business processes and services.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot; http://www.tibco.com/products/automation/application-integration/activematrix-businessworks/default.jsp&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Learn more about TIBCO ActiveMatrix BusinessWorks™&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;br&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="shortDesc">
            <value language="en">&lt;p&gt;TIBCO ActiveMatrix BusinessWorks™ is TIBCO’s flagship SOA automation platform that enables users to develop new services, orchestrate business processes and integrate applications with little or no coding. &lt;/p&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
    </attributes>
    <skus>
        <sku guid="60519A22-ED07-424C-063F-8ACFE2AAD66A">
            <code>TIBAMB11F</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Type">
                    <skuoptionvalue>Enterprise</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-03-01T00:00:00-08:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true">
                <file>software.exe</file>
                <downloadexpiry>0</downloadexpiry>
                <downloadlimit>0</downloadlimit>
            </digitalasset>
            <image>blank-box.png</image>
            <attributes>
                <attribute key="EULA">
                    <value>eula_1.htm</value>
                </attribute>
            </attributes>
        </sku>
    </skus>
    <seo>
        <url>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </url>
        <title>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </title>
        <keywords>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </keywords>
        <description>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </description>
    </seo>
</product>

<product>
    <code>TIBEMS111</code>
    <name>
        <value language="fr"></value>
        <value language="en">Enterprise Message Service</value>
    </name>
    <type>product</type>
    <taxcode>GOODS</taxcode>
    <brand>Tibco</brand>
    <image>blank-box.png</image>
    <availability>
        <storevisible>true</storevisible>
        <notsoldseperately>false</notsoldseperately>
        <enabledate>2013-03-01T09:48:00-08:00</enabledate>
        <minorderqty>1</minorderqty>
        <availabilityrule>ALWAYS_AVAILABLE</availabilityrule>
        <orderlimit>0</orderlimit>
    </availability>
    <attributes>
        <attribute key="longDesc">
            <value>N/A</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="features">
            <value>&lt;div class=&quot;intro-only&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Businesses have become increasingly dependent on the real-time flow of information. When it isn't available for decision-making, or when data is locked in databases, you can't execute, capture value from your critical information assets, or compete in the way you want, in the way that delights customers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;TIBCO Enterprise Message Service™ (EMS) is a standards-based messaging platform that brings together IT assets and communications technologies on a common high-performance messaging backbone. EMS scales horizontally to support real-time decision-making across the organization, to unlock data siloed in databases and applications, and to power business operations for fast, event-driven execution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;spaced&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reduce Cost, Complexity, and Time:&lt;/strong&gt; Integrate disparate systems using a common backbone that supports open standards, existing systems, and native support for a broad range of technologies for servers, desktops, and mobile devices including C, COBOL, Java EE, and .NET.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Secure Leading Performance, Scalability, and Reliability:&lt;/strong&gt; Leverage TIBCO's integrated suite of products for fast implementation of 21st Century architectures and increased development and operations productivity.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enable Access to Information On the Go:&lt;/strong&gt; Extend the high performance enterprise messaging backbone to web and mobile devices with TIBCO Web Messaging for TIBCO EMS.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Remove Single Points of Failure:&lt;/strong&gt; Integrate into a distributed and reliable architecture with load-balancing, routing, and fault tolerant configurations that can reliably deliver high-throughput messaging with 99.99% uptime.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deliver Secure Messaging:&lt;/strong&gt; Support security and administrative control including SSL for client-to-server and server-to-server connectivity and plug-in security for custom-built authentication (JAAS).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support Demanding Applications:&lt;/strong&gt; Support several protocols on the same platform and several quality of service levels – and supply broad messaging semantics and different messaging including externally managed XA-compliant transactions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;							
															
															
															
															
						&lt;/p&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="benefits">
            <value>&lt;div id=&quot;featureAttributeDiv&quot;&gt;
																		
				&lt;p&gt;Common messaging platform enabling the delivery of information using leading platforms, standards, and development technologies;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Multiple service protocols and qualities of service supported, providing one of the broadest sets of messaging semantics and options to optimize performance and service levels;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Distributed architecture avoids introduction of a single point of failure with support for load-balancing, routing, and fault tolerant configurations;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Administrative control to maintain a high performance and secure messaging solution, and supports security standards including SSL.
			&lt;br&gt;
		
														&lt;/div&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="shortDesc">
            <value language="en">&lt;p&gt;TIBCO Enterprise Message Service™ is a standards-based enterprise messaging platform that brings together different IT assets and communications technologies on a common real-time backbone and manages the real-time flow of information. &lt;/p&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
    </attributes>
    <skus>
        <sku guid="B5E64DA8-5F70-E6DD-B0EF-4EA8112372AA">
            <code>TIBEMS111E</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Type">
                    <skuoptionvalue>Enterprise</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-03-01T00:00:00-08:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true">
                <file>software.exe</file>
                <downloadexpiry>0</downloadexpiry>
                <downloadlimit>0</downloadlimit>
            </digitalasset>
            <image>blank-box.png</image>
            <attributes>
                <attribute key="EULA">
                    <value>eula_1.htm</value>
                </attribute>
            </attributes>
        </sku>
    </skus>
    <seo>
        <url>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </url>
        <title>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </title>
        <keywords>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </keywords>
        <description>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </description>
    </seo>
</product>

<product>
    <code>TIBRAN111</code>
    <name>
        <value language="fr"></value>
        <value language="en">Rendezvous Software</value>
    </name>
    <type>product</type>
    <taxcode>GOODS</taxcode>
    <brand>Tibco</brand>
    <image>blank-box.png</image>
    <availability>
        <storevisible>true</storevisible>
        <notsoldseperately>false</notsoldseperately>
        <enabledate>2013-03-01T09:55:00-08:00</enabledate>
        <minorderqty>1</minorderqty>
        <availabilityrule>ALWAYS_AVAILABLE</availabilityrule>
        <orderlimit>0</orderlimit>
    </availability>
    <attributes>
        <attribute key="longDesc">
            <value>&lt;p&gt; 	       TIBCO Rendezvous® is the leading messaging product for real-time, multicast-based broad data distribution. It has been used by thousands of customers for more than a decade, and is the backbone for several of the largest mission-critical systems in production today.
 
   &lt;/p&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="features">
            <value>&lt;div style=&quot;width: 390px;&quot; class=&quot;column-main&quot;&gt;
							
								&lt;div class=&quot;intro-only&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;TIBCO Rendezvous® is the industry-leading – and most widely deployed – low latency messaging and data distribution solution on the market. Proven by thousands of organizations worldwide, Rendezvous high-performance messaging middleware supports applications ranging from market data distribution and trading to real-time control systems, supply chains, and transportation networks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;With Rendezvous' flexible and scalable information bus infrastructure, you can build event-driven applications that unlock value from big data while it's in motion and before it enters a database.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rendezvous supplies a bandwidth-efficient, flexible platform for global application infrastructure. Its APIs for Java, C, C++, C#, Perl, and COM let you develop robust event-driven applications using the full capabilities of high-performance multi-processor servers and advanced networks. And to ensure low-latency, you can embed the TIBCO Rendezvous In-Process Module directly into your applications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For extreme low-latency messaging performance, Rendezvous natively integrates with TIBCO FTL®, and with TIBCO Enterprise Message Service™ for JMS-compliant enterprise messaging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul class=&quot;spaced&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Increase Throughput and Data Distribution:&lt;/strong&gt; Optimize network utilization for peer-to-peer multicast-based messaging.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Easily Manage Quality of Service:&lt;/strong&gt; Choose delivery levels from reliable to certified.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Increase Efficiency and Simplify Configurations:&lt;/strong&gt; Implement dynamic, source-based routing with interest-driven forwarding across multiple messaging domains.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lower Administration Costs:&lt;/strong&gt; Use centralized daemon management and self-managing protocols.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Improve Performance and Flexibility:&lt;/strong&gt; Rely on user extensible types for messaging.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Centralize Management:&lt;/strong&gt; Monitor and manage daemons, subjects, and multicast groups remotely via a browser interface or Java API.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;							
															
															
															
															
						&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="benefits">
            <value>&lt;div id=&quot;featureAttributeDiv&quot;&gt;
																		
				&lt;p&gt;Messaging can be publish/subscribe or request/reply, point-to-point or multicast, synchronous or asynchronous, and delivered via the local-area network (LAN), wide-area network (WAN), or the internet;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Choice of qualities of service from lightweight informational messages to reliable and certified delivery;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Peer-to-peer multicast-based messaging for efficient network utilization and scalability;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TIBCO Rendezvous® In-Process Module that embeds Rendezvous capabilities directly into applications for ultra-low latency needs;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Point-to-point and Wide Area Network (WAN) messaging support via TCP and SSL;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dynamic, source-based routing with interest driven forwarding provides added efficiency and simplified configuration across multiple messaging domains.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;br&gt;
		
														&lt;/div&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="shortDesc">
            <value language="en">&lt;p&gt; 	       TIBCO Rendezvous® is the leading messaging product for real-time, multicast-based broad data distribution.  
   &lt;/p&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
    </attributes>
    <skus>
        <sku guid="E848430D-A08D-4928-5696-44EBDE5268A7">
            <code>TIBRAN111E</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Type">
                    <skuoptionvalue>Enterprise</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-03-01T00:00:00-08:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true">
                <file>software.exe</file>
                <downloadexpiry>0</downloadexpiry>
                <downloadlimit>0</downloadlimit>
            </digitalasset>
            <image>blank-box.png</image>
            <attributes>
                <attribute key="EULA">
                    <value>eula_1.htm</value>
                </attribute>
            </attributes>
        </sku>
    </skus>
    <seo>
        <url>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </url>
        <title>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </title>
        <keywords>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </keywords>
        <description>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </description>
    </seo>
</product>

<product>
    <code>BKUP</code>
    <name>
        <value language="fr"></value>
        <value language="en">Norton™ AntiVirus Backup Media</value>
    </name>
    <type>media</type>
    <taxcode>GOODS</taxcode>
    <brand>Symantec</brand>
    <image>norton-anti-virus.png</image>
    <availability>
        <storevisible>false</storevisible>
        <notsoldseperately>false</notsoldseperately>
        <enabledate>2013-03-01T15:48:00-08:00</enabledate>
        <minorderqty>1</minorderqty>
        <availabilityrule>ALWAYS_AVAILABLE</availabilityrule>
        <orderlimit>0</orderlimit>
    </availability>
    <attributes>
        <attribute key="longDesc">
            <value>n/a</value>
        </attribute>
    </attributes>
    <skus>
        <sku guid="7C73C6A0-0C3A-CA84-5060-CE499D49BAEE">
            <code>BKUP</code>
            <shippable enabled="true">
                <weight units="KG">0.00</weight>
                <width units="CM">0.00</width>
                <length units="CM">0.00</length>
                <height units="CM">0.00</height>
            </shippable>
            <digitalasset enabled="false"/>
        </sku>
    </skus>
    <seo>
        <url>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </url>
        <title>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </title>
        <keywords>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </keywords>
        <description>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </description>
    </seo>
</product>

<product>
    <code>BKUP360</code>
    <name>
        <value language="fr"></value>
        <value language="en">Norton 360™ Backup CD</value>
    </name>
    <type>media</type>
    <taxcode>GOODS</taxcode>
    <brand>Symantec</brand>
    <image>norton-360.png</image>
    <availability>
        <storevisible>true</storevisible>
        <notsoldseperately>false</notsoldseperately>
        <enabledate>2013-03-01T16:35:00-08:00</enabledate>
        <minorderqty>1</minorderqty>
        <availabilityrule>ALWAYS_AVAILABLE</availabilityrule>
        <orderlimit>0</orderlimit>
    </availability>
    <attributes>
        <attribute key="longDesc">
            <value>N/A</value>
        </attribute>
    </attributes>
    <skus>
        <sku guid="2F83DFF3-B0BC-8970-6A91-AFAF53E223B0">
            <code>BKUP360</code>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true"/>
        </sku>
    </skus>
    <seo>
        <url>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </url>
        <title>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </title>
        <keywords>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </keywords>
        <description>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </description>
    </seo>
</product>

<product>
    <code>N360REN</code>
    <name>
        <value language="fr"></value>
        <value language="en">Norton 360™ Renewal</value>
    </name>
    <type>renewal</type>
    <taxcode>GOODS</taxcode>
    <brand>Symantec</brand>
    <image>norton-360.png</image>
    <availability>
        <storevisible>true</storevisible>
        <notsoldseperately>false</notsoldseperately>
        <enabledate>2013-03-01T18:00:00-08:00</enabledate>
        <minorderqty>1</minorderqty>
        <availabilityrule>ALWAYS_AVAILABLE</availabilityrule>
        <orderlimit>0</orderlimit>
    </availability>
    <attributes>
        <attribute key="system_requirements">
            <value>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Operating Systems Supported&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft® Windows® XP (32-bit) Home/Professional/Tablet PC/Media Center (32-bit) with Service Pack 2 or later&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Windows Vista® (32-bit and 64-bit) Starter/Home Basic/Home Premium/Business/Ultimate with Service Pack 1 or later&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Windows 7 (32-bit and 64-bit) Starter/Home Basic/Home Premium/Professional/Ultimate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Windows 8 and Windows 8 Pro (32-bit and 64-bit)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum Hardware Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;300 MHz for Microsoft Windows XP, 1 GHz for Microsoft Windows Vista/Microsoft Windows 7/Windows 8&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;256 MB of RAM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;300 MB of available hard disk space&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CD-ROM or DVD drive (if not installing via electronic download)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Browser Support for Phishing Protection, Safe Search, and Password Management&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot; style=&quot;margin-bottom: 3px;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Internet Explorer® 7.0 or higher (32-bit only)&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mozilla® Firefox® (32-bit only)&lt;sup&gt;1,2&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Google Chrome™&lt;sup&gt;1,2&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Browser Support for Vulnerability Protection&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot; style=&quot;margin-bottom: 3px;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Internet Explorer® 7.0 or higher (32-bit only)&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mozilla® Firefox® (32-bit only)&lt;sup&gt;1,2&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support for Antispam&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Outlook® 2002 or later&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Outlook Express 6.0 or later&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Windows Mail (spam filtering only)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="longDesc">
            <value>&lt;p&gt;Our ultimate Internet and antivirus protection for all you do online&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provides proactive protection, so you can do what you want online, knowing you’re protected.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ultra-fast Internet detection layer stops most threats before they can even reach your computer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Powerful threat-removal layer targets and eliminates even the hardest to remove infections. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;na</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="features">
            <value>&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;span style=&quot;color: red; margin: 0 0 0 0;&quot;&gt;FEATURES&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our ultimate protection for your PC&lt;/strong&gt; – includes everything from Norton™ AntiVirus and Norton™ Internet Security with 2 GB of secured online storage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;span style=&quot;color: red; margin: 0 0 0 0;&quot;&gt;EXCLUSIVE&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norton&lt;/strong&gt;™&lt;strong&gt; Protection System&lt;/strong&gt; – Our 5 patented layers of protection detect and eliminate threats more quickly and accurately than other technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Network Defense Layer Protection&lt;/strong&gt; – Stops online threats before they can reach your computer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;span style=&quot;color: red; margin: 0 0 0 0;&quot;&gt;IMPROVED&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SONAR Behavioral Protection &amp;amp; Live 24x7 Threat Monitoring &lt;/strong&gt;– Stays ahead of, detects and eliminates threats that haven’t been invented yet by watching your PC for suspicious activity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;span style=&quot;color: red; margin: 0 0 0 0;&quot;&gt;NEW&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Threat-removal Layer &lt;/strong&gt;– Targets and eliminates hard-to-remove threats less sophisticated products often miss.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;span style=&quot;color: red; margin: 0 0 0 0;&quot;&gt;EXCLUSIVE&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norton&lt;/strong&gt;™ &lt;strong&gt;Management&lt;/strong&gt; – Cloud-based controls let you fix, update, renew and install Norton 360™ over the Internet with a few simple clicks. It brings together your available Norton™ protection for other devices, like your Mac® computer, smartphone or tablet, in one place.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norton&lt;/strong&gt;™&lt;strong&gt; Safe Web for Facebook &lt;/strong&gt;– Scans your Facebook News Feed for dangerous links, infected downloads and unsafe websites.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Automatic Backup &lt;/strong&gt;– Backs up your photos, music and other important files only when you’re not using your computer, so it won’t get in your way and you don’t have to remember to do it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PC Tuneup&lt;/strong&gt; – Fixes common computer problems, frees up memory, removes unnecessary files and cleans up your hard drive.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;span style=&quot;color: red; margin: 0 0 0 0;&quot;&gt;NEW&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Always up-to-date Product Version&lt;/strong&gt; – Norton™ automatically sends you important product and feature updates throughout the year. The latest version installs without you needing to do anything.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FREE 24x7 Support&lt;/strong&gt; – Offers you expert help and answers by phone, live chat or online, whenever you need them. &lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;span style=&quot;color: red; margin: 0 0 0 0;&quot;&gt;EXCLUSIVE&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Parental Controls Management&lt;/strong&gt; – Lets you access Norton™ Online Family through Norton 360™.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Antiphishing Technology&lt;/strong&gt; – Blocks fraudulent “phishing” websites set up by online scammers to steal your money, passwords, and identity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norton&lt;/strong&gt;™&lt;strong&gt; Identity Safe &lt;/strong&gt;– Remembers, secures and automatically enters your user names and passwords for you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;span style=&quot;color: red; margin: 0 0 0 0;&quot;&gt;EXCLUSIVE&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Insight&lt;/strong&gt; – Improves performance by identifying safe files and only scanning unknown files.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norton&lt;/strong&gt;™&lt;strong&gt; Safe Web&lt;/strong&gt; – Proactively protects you while you surf the Web by warning of and blocking unsafe and fake websites right in your search results.&lt;sup&gt;2&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Browser Protection&lt;/strong&gt; – Proactively protects you by checking for and blocking online threats as your browser loads, to stop online threats before they can do damage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Web-Based Backup Access&lt;/strong&gt; – - Lets you download and share photos, videos and other files you’ve backed up online, anytime, anywhere via the cloud.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Download Insight 2.0&lt;/strong&gt; – Protects you from dangerous applications before you install them by telling you if they are harmful or unstable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vulnerability Protection&lt;/strong&gt; – Stops cybercriminals from using security holes (vulnerabilities) in applications to sneak threats onto your PC.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;span style=&quot;color: red; margin: 0 0 0 0;&quot;&gt;IMPROVED&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bandwidth Management 2.0&lt;/strong&gt; – Automatically adjusts Norton™ data usage updates when you connect to 3G networks to avoid using up your monthly data allotment or causing overage fees.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;span style=&quot;color: red; margin: 0 0 0 0;&quot;&gt;EXCLUSIVE&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norton&lt;/strong&gt;™&lt;strong&gt; Pulse Updates&lt;/strong&gt; – Updates your protection every 5 to 15 minutes, without disrupting you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="benefits">
            <value>&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Say goodbye to viruses&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It's okay to blink, because we never do – SONAR technology and live 24x7 Threat Monitoring watch over your PC for any suspicious behavior to quickly identify threats.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Download away – we scan the files you download and eliminate online threats that we find.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep clean your PC – our powerful Threat-Removal Layer targets and scrubs out aggressive, hard-to-remove infections that less sophisticated products often miss. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Harness global power – only Norton™ can bring you the ultra-fast Network Defense Layer to block a multitude of threats before they can even touch your PC.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protection from the future, available today – our exclusive reputation and behavior antivirus technology are so advanced that they can stop online threats that bad guys haven't even created yet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep out trespassers – Browser Protection blocks unsafe websites that secretly download software that can steal personal information or take over your PC.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Neutralize online identity thieves – it's the only way to shop, surf and visit social networks without worry&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It's easy to stumble into the wrong part of the web – we block &quot;phishing&quot; websites set up to trick you into leaking your passwords, credit card numbers or worse.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Facebook links are tempting – now you don't need to worry if a Facebook News Feed contains dangerous downloads or fraudulent links.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protects your identity by securely storing and automatically entering your user names and passwords.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Help keep kids safe from Internet dangers with Norton&lt;/strong&gt;™&lt;strong&gt; Online Family&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Easily connects you to Norton™ Online Family right from within your Norton™ Control Center.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lets you know what your kids are up to online by tracking which websites they visit, and allows you to block inappropriate sites.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keeps an eye on your kids’ social network activities and who they’re chatting with online, so you can spot potential dangers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Engineered to go unnoticed – because great protection doesn't get in your way or slow you down&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blazingly fast performance delivers fast browsing and file scanning.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intelligent detection and quiet background operation block threats and won’t overload you with pop-up warnings or restart requests.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;So smart, it scans and runs updates only when you’re not using your PC – with no need to reboot after updates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Everyone's talking cloud. And with our new Cloud-based Norton&lt;/strong&gt;™&lt;strong&gt; Management, it’s easy to stay in control&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lets you fix, update, renew or install Norton™ products on additional PCs without needing to track down the product key or install CD. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works from anywhere over the Internet with a few simple clicks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accidents happen. Hard drives fail. Coffee gets spilled. Make sure you always have a backup.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Automatic backup takes care of your photos, music, and other important files and backs them up to a disc, USB device, or online to one of our secure data centers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protects files you back up online with government-grade encryption.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lets you get up and running fast - Norton™ backup restores files with just a few clicks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PC need a pick me up? Keep it running fast and trouble-free with our exclusive clean up and tuneup features.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixes common problems that can slow down or cause your PC to crash or freeze.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gets rid of unnecessary files and optimizes your hard drive.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Frees up system memory.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="shortDesc">
            <value language="en">Our ultimate Internet and antivirus protection for all you do online.  Introducing the new Norton 360™.</value>
        </attribute>
    </attributes>
    <skus>
        <sku guid="0CCABE45-EE64-04D0-78DF-F05EAB157051">
            <code>N360REN2</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Type">
                    <skuoptionvalue>2year</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-03-01T00:00:00-08:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true">
                <file>software.exe</file>
                <downloadexpiry>0</downloadexpiry>
                <downloadlimit>0</downloadlimit>
            </digitalasset>
            <image>BX_N360_Y13_r_r_EN_342.png</image>
            <attributes/>
        </sku>
        <sku guid="1A288E72-0F67-3D71-B892-BD4EAEF58466">
            <code>N360REN</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Type">
                    <skuoptionvalue>1year</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-03-01T00:00:00-08:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true">
                <file>software.exe</file>
                <downloadexpiry>0</downloadexpiry>
                <downloadlimit>0</downloadlimit>
            </digitalasset>
            <image>norton-360.png</image>
            <attributes/>
        </sku>
    </skus>
    <seo>
        <url>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </url>
        <title>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </title>
        <keywords>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </keywords>
        <description>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </description>
    </seo>
</product>

<product>
    <code>NL1PC</code>
    <name>
        <value language="fr"></value>
        <value language="en">NortonLive™ Spyware and Virus Removal</value>
    </name>
    <type>service</type>
    <taxcode>GOODS</taxcode>
    <brand>Symantec</brand>
    <image>blank-box.png</image>
    <availability>
        <storevisible>true</storevisible>
        <notsoldseperately>false</notsoldseperately>
        <enabledate>2013-03-01T11:53:00-08:00</enabledate>
        <minorderqty>1</minorderqty>
        <availabilityrule>ALWAYS_AVAILABLE</availabilityrule>
        <orderlimit>0</orderlimit>
    </availability>
    <attributes>
        <attribute key="system_requirements">
            <value>&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
Microsoft® Windows® XP SP2 or higher, Windows Vista®, or Windows 7; Internet Explorer® 6.0 or later; high speed Internet connection (recommended); 800 MHz processor (recommended); 512 MB of RAM (recommended).
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="longDesc">
            <value>Expert help to eliminate viruses and other computer threats</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="features">
            <value>&lt;ul class=&quot;bullet&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;span&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Finds and removes stubborn viruses, spyware, worms and other threats.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;span&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Performs a 9-point threat detection and elimination service.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;span&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Stops annoying pop-up ads and alerts caused by spyware.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;span&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Identifies and fixes security problems that could allow threats to sneak in.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;span&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Patches known Windows® security holes.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;span&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Updates Norton software and virus definitions (if applicable).&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;span&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Gives you simple tips for avoiding future infections.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="benefits">
            <value>&lt;p&gt;
	    &lt;span&gt;
	        &lt;span&gt;If your computer has been infected, you can call us at 1 (888) 210-9603 for immediate help.&lt;/span&gt;
	    &lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
	    &lt;span&gt;
	        &lt;span&gt;Is your computer constantly crashing? Are you bombarded with annoying pop-ups? You could have a virus or spyware on your computer. Let NortonLive Spyware and Virus Removal Service get you back on track.&lt;/span&gt;
	    &lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
	    &lt;span&gt;
	        &lt;span&gt;Our certified experts are available 24/7 to eliminate deeply rooted viruses, spyware and other malicious software right over the Internet, so you don't even have to leave your home or office.&lt;/span&gt;
	    &lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
	    &lt;span&gt;
	        &lt;span&gt;NortonLive even helps prevent future infections by patching known Windows® security holes and fixing any other security problems that could allow threats to sneak in.&lt;/span&gt;
	    &lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
	    &lt;span&gt;
	        &lt;span&gt;Save yourself time and frustration - call a NortonLive Expert today.&lt;/span&gt;
	    &lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;/p&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="shortDesc">
            <value language="en">Expert help to eliminate viruses and other computer threats</value>
        </attribute>
    </attributes>
    <skus>
        <sku guid="4493E2DC-A41C-21AD-99BD-F4FA267461F6">
            <code>NLPC1</code>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true"/>
        </sku>
    </skus>
    <seo>
        <url>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </url>
        <title>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </title>
        <keywords>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </keywords>
        <description>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </description>
    </seo>
</product>

<product>
    <code>BKUPGH</code>
    <name>
        <value language="fr"></value>
        <value language="en">Norton Ghost 16 Backup CD</value>
    </name>
    <type>media</type>
    <taxcode>GOODS</taxcode>
    <brand>Symantec</brand>
    <image>norton-ghost.png</image>
    <availability>
        <storevisible>true</storevisible>
        <notsoldseperately>false</notsoldseperately>
        <enabledate>2013-03-01T16:39:00-08:00</enabledate>
        <minorderqty>1</minorderqty>
        <availabilityrule>ALWAYS_AVAILABLE</availabilityrule>
        <orderlimit>0</orderlimit>
    </availability>
    <attributes>
        <attribute key="longDesc">
            <value>N/A</value>
        </attribute>
    </attributes>
    <skus>
        <sku guid="C379449A-AFF1-B3DB-65EB-D842E321C51A">
            <code>BKUPGH</code>
            <shippable enabled="true">
                <weight units="KG">0.00</weight>
                <width units="CM">0.00</width>
                <length units="CM">0.00</length>
                <height units="CM">0.00</height>
            </shippable>
            <digitalasset enabled="false"/>
        </sku>
    </skus>
    <seo>
        <url>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </url>
        <title>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </title>
        <keywords>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </keywords>
        <description>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </description>
    </seo>
</product>

<product>
    <code>NAV111</code>
    <name>
        <value language="fr"></value>
        <value language="en">Norton™ AntiVirus</value>
    </name>
    <type>product</type>
    <taxcode>GOODS</taxcode>
    <brand>Symantec</brand>
    <image>norton-anti-virus.png</image>
    <availability>
        <storevisible>true</storevisible>
        <notsoldseperately>false</notsoldseperately>
        <enabledate>2013-03-01T17:58:00-08:00</enabledate>
        <minorderqty>1</minorderqty>
        <availabilityrule>ALWAYS_AVAILABLE</availabilityrule>
        <orderlimit>0</orderlimit>
    </availability>
    <attributes>
        <attribute key="system_requirements">
            <value>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Operating Systems Supported&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft® Windows® XP (32-bit) Home/Professional/Tablet PC/Media Center (32-bit) with Service Pack 2 or later&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Windows Vista® (32-bit and 64-bit) Starter/Home Basic/Home Premium/Business/Ultimate with Service Pack 1 or later&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Windows 7 (32-bit and 64-bit) Starter/Home Basic/Home Premium/Professional/Ultimate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Windows 8 and Windows 8 Pro (32-bit and 64-bit)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum Hardware Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;300 MHz for Microsoft Windows XP, 1 GHz for Microsoft Windows Vista/Microsoft Windows 7/Windows 8&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;256 MB of RAM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;300 MB of available hard disk space&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CD-ROM or DVD drive (if not installing via electronic download)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Browser Support for Vulnerability Protection&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot; style=&quot;margin-bottom: 3px;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Internet Explorer® 7.0 or higher (32-bit only)&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mozilla® Firefox® (32-bit only)&lt;sup&gt;1,2&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="bannerName">
            <value language="en">norton-antivirus-banner.png</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="longDesc">
            <value>&lt;p&gt;Basic antivirus protection that stops viruses and spyware, so you can safely go online and share.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Five patented layers of protection quickly and accurately detect and eliminate viruses and spyware.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lets you download and freely share without getting or passing on viruses.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protects your privacy and prevents your passwords and identity from being stolen when you surf the Web.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="features">
            <value>&lt;h3&gt;EXCLUSIVE&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norton Protection System&lt;/strong&gt; – Our 5 patented layers of protection detect and eliminate threats more quickly and accurately than other technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Browser Protection&lt;/strong&gt; – Proactively protects you by checking for and blocking online threats as your browser loads, to stop online threats before they can do damage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;IMPROVED&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SONAR Behavioral Protection &amp;amp; Live 24x7 Threat Monitoring&lt;/strong&gt; – Stays ahead of, detects and eliminates threats that haven’t been invented yet by watching your PC for suspicious activity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;NEW&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Threat-removal Layer&lt;/strong&gt; – Targets and eliminates hard-to-remove threats less sophisticated products often miss.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;EXCLUSIVE&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Insight&lt;/strong&gt; – Improves performance by identifying safe files and only scanning unknown files. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Download Insight 2.0 &lt;/strong&gt;– Protects you from dangerous applications before you install them by telling you if they are harmful or unstable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;NEW&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Always up-to-date Product Version&lt;/strong&gt; – Norton automatically sends you important product and feature updates throughout the year. The latest version installs without you needing to do anything.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FREE 24x7 Support &lt;/strong&gt;– Offers you expert help and answers by phone, live chat or online, whenever you need them.&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;EXCLUSIVE&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norton Management&lt;/strong&gt; – Cloud-based controls let you fix, update, renew and install Norton AntiVirus over the Internet with a few simple clicks. It brings together your available Norton protection for other devices, like your Mac® computer, smartphone or tablet, in one place.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;IMPROVED&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bandwidth Management 2.0 &lt;/strong&gt;– Automatically adjusts Norton data usage updates when you connect to 3G networks to avoid using up your monthly data allotment or causing overage fees.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vulnerability Protection &lt;/strong&gt;– Stops cybercriminals from using security holes (vulnerabilities) in applications to sneak threats onto your PC.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;EXCLUSIVE&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norton Pulse Updates &lt;/strong&gt;– Updates your protection every 5 to 15 minutes, without disrupting you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="benefits">
            <value>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Free Trial - Norton™ AntiVirus&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Click on the button below to start downloading a  FREE 30-day trial of the full product with no obligation. See  additional installation instructions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h3 class=&quot;mod&quot;&gt;Benefits&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;mod&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Say goodbye to viruses&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It's okay to blink, because we never do – SONAR technology and live 24x7 Threat Monitoring watch over your PC for any suspicious behavior to quickly identify threats.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Download away – we scan the files you download and eliminate online threats that we find.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep clean your PC – our powerful Threat-Removal Layer targets and scrubs out aggressive, hard-to-remove infections that less sophisticated products often miss. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Harness global power – only Norton can bring you the ultra-fast Network Defense Layer to block a multitude of threats before they can even touch your PC.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protection from the future, available today – our exclusive reputation and behavior antivirus technology are so advanced that they can stop online threats that bad guys haven't even created yet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep out trespassers – Browser Protection blocks unsafe websites that secretly download software that can steal personal information or take over your PC.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shop, surf and visit social networks without worry&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It's easy to stumble into the wrong part of the web – we block &quot;phishing&quot; websites set up to trick you into leaking your passwords, credit card numbers or worse.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Facebook links are tempting – now you don't need to worry if a Facebook News Feed contains dangerous downloads or fraudulent links.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protects your identity by securely storing and automatically entering your user names and passwords.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Engineered to go unnoticed – because great protection doesn't get in your way or slow you down&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blazingly fast performance delivers fast browsing and file scanning.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intelligent detection and quiet background operation block threats and won’t overload you with pop-up warnings or restart requests.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;So smart, it scans and runs updates only when you’re not using your PC—with no need to reboot after updates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Everyone's talking cloud. And with our new Cloud-based Norton Management, it’s easy to stay in control&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lets you fix, update, renew or install Norton products on additional PCs without needing to track down the product key or install CD. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works from anywhere over the Internet with a few simple clicks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="shortDesc">
            <value language="en">Keep your computer safe from viruses and spyware with the industry’s most powerful protection.</value>
        </attribute>
    </attributes>
    <skus>
        <sku guid="7DE5C396-03BC-57DB-9F4F-FAA55ED7ABF0">
            <code>NAV1115UR</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Type">
                    <skuoptionvalue>5user</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-03-01T00:00:00-08:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true">
                <file>software.exe</file>
                <downloadexpiry>0</downloadexpiry>
                <downloadlimit>0</downloadlimit>
            </digitalasset>
            <image>norton-anti-virus.png</image>
            <attributes>
                <attribute key="EULA">
                    <value>eula_2.htm</value>
                </attribute>
            </attributes>
        </sku>
        <sku guid="02A33E29-3524-7469-146B-AB77095C9CF2">
            <code>NAV111U</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Type">
                    <skuoptionvalue>Upgrade</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-03-01T00:00:00-08:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true">
                <file>software.exe</file>
                <downloadexpiry>0</downloadexpiry>
                <downloadlimit>0</downloadlimit>
            </digitalasset>
            <image>norton-anti-virus.png</image>
            <attributes>
                <attribute key="EULA">
                    <value>eula_2.htm</value>
                </attribute>
            </attributes>
        </sku>
        <sku guid="BA2759B5-07CA-CF77-1645-DAC5389FE078">
            <code>NAV1111YR</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Type">
                    <skuoptionvalue>1year</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-03-01T00:00:00-08:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true">
                <file>software.exe</file>
                <downloadexpiry>0</downloadexpiry>
                <downloadlimit>0</downloadlimit>
            </digitalasset>
            <image>norton-anti-virus.png</image>
            <attributes>
                <attribute key="EULA">
                    <value>eula_2.htm</value>
                </attribute>
            </attributes>
        </sku>
        <sku guid="34CABBD3-4A81-8CAD-10DD-3E9D92D9E9F3">
            <code>NAV1112YR</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Type">
                    <skuoptionvalue>2year</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-03-01T00:00:00-08:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true">
                <file>software.exe</file>
                <downloadexpiry>0</downloadexpiry>
                <downloadlimit>0</downloadlimit>
            </digitalasset>
            <image>norton-anti-virus.png</image>
            <attributes>
                <attribute key="EULA">
                    <value>eula_2.htm</value>
                </attribute>
            </attributes>
        </sku>
    </skus>
    <seo>
        <url>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </url>
        <title>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </title>
        <keywords>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </keywords>
        <description>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </description>
    </seo>
</product>

<product>
    <code>NAV333</code>
    <name>
        <value language="fr"></value>
        <value language="en">Norton™ Internet Security</value>
    </name>
    <type>product</type>
    <taxcode>GOODS</taxcode>
    <brand>Symantec</brand>
    <image>norton-internet-security.png</image>
    <availability>
        <storevisible>true</storevisible>
        <notsoldseperately>false</notsoldseperately>
        <enabledate>2013-03-01T18:23:00-08:00</enabledate>
        <minorderqty>1</minorderqty>
        <availabilityrule>ALWAYS_AVAILABLE</availabilityrule>
        <orderlimit>0</orderlimit>
    </availability>
    <attributes>
        <attribute key="system_requirements">
            <value>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Operating Systems Supported&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft® Windows® XP (32-bit) Home/Professional/Tablet PC/Media Center (32-bit) with Service Pack 2 or later&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Windows Vista® (32-bit and 64-bit) Starter/Home Basic/Home Premium/Business/Ultimate with Service Pack 1 or later&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Windows 7 (32-bit and 64-bit) Starter/Home Basic/Home Premium/Professional/Ultimate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Windows 8 and Windows 8 Pro (32-bit and 64-bit)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum Hardware Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;300 MHz for Microsoft Windows XP, 1 GHz for Microsoft Windows Vista/Microsoft Windows 7/Windows 8&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;256 MB of RAM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;300 MB of available hard disk space&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CD-ROM or DVD drive (if not installing via electronic download)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Browser Support for Phishing Protection, Safe Search, and Password Management&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot; style=&quot;margin-bottom: 3px;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Internet Explorer® 7.0 or higher (32-bit only)&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mozilla® Firefox® (32-bit only)&lt;sup&gt;1,2&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Google Chrome™&lt;sup&gt;1,2&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;span style=&quot;margin: 0 0 0 25px;&quot;&gt;&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;As made available by Symantec within your service period.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;margin: 0 0 0 25px;&quot;&gt;&lt;sup&gt;2&lt;/sup&gt;Supports current and the most recent previous 32-bit major releases.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Browser Support for Vulnerability Protection&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot; style=&quot;margin-bottom: 3px;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Internet Explorer® 7.0 or higher (32-bit only)&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mozilla® Firefox® (32-bit only)&lt;sup&gt;1,2&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;span style=&quot;margin: 0 0 0 25px;&quot;&gt;&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;As made available by Symantec within your service period.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;margin: 0 0 0 25px;&quot;&gt;&lt;sup&gt;2&lt;/sup&gt;Supports current and the most recent previous 32-bit major releases.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support for Antispam&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Outlook® 2002 or later&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Outlook Express 6.0 or later&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Windows Mail (spam filtering only)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="bannerName">
            <value language="en">norton-internet-security-banner.png</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="longDesc">
            <value>&lt;p&gt;Advanced Internet and antivirus protection for anywhere you go and anything you do online.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provides proactive protection, so you can do what you want online, knowing you’re protected&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improved SONAR technology and live 24x7 global threat monitoring stay ahead of emerging threats&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ultra-fast Internet detection layer stops most threats before they can even reach your computer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="features">
            <value>&lt;h3&gt;FEATURES&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advanced protection for your PC &lt;/strong&gt;– includes everything from Norton AntiVirus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;EXCLUSIVE&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norton Protection System&lt;/strong&gt; – Our 5 patented layers of protection detect and eliminate threats more quickly and accurately than other technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Network Defense Layer Protection&lt;/strong&gt; – Stops online threats before they can reach your computer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;IMPROVED&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SONAR Behavioral Protection &amp;amp; Live 24x7 Threat Monitoring&lt;/strong&gt; – Stays ahead of, detects and eliminates threats that haven’t been invented yet by watching your PC for suspicious activity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;NEW&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Threat-removal Layer&lt;/strong&gt; – Targets and eliminates hard-to-remove threats less sophisticated products often miss.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;EXCLUSIVE&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norton Management&lt;/strong&gt; – Cloud-based controls let you fix, update, renew and install Norton Internet Security over the Internet with a few simple clicks. It brings together your available Norton protection for other devices, like your Mac® computer, smartphone or tablet, in one place.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;NEW&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Always up-to-date Product Version&lt;/strong&gt; – Norton automatically sends you important product and feature updates throughout the year. The latest version installs without you needing to do anything.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norton Identity Safe&lt;/strong&gt; – Remembers, secures and automatically enters your user names and passwords for you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norton Safe Web for Facebook&lt;/strong&gt; – Scans your Facebook News Feed for dangerous links, infected downloads and unsafe websites.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;EXCLUSIVE&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Parental Controls Management&lt;/strong&gt; – Lets you access Norton Online Family through Norton Internet Security&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FREE 24x7 Support&lt;/strong&gt; – Offers you expert help and answers by phone, live chat, or online, whenever you need them.&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Antiphishing Technology &lt;/strong&gt;– Blocks fraudulent “phishing” websites set up by online scammers to steal your money, passwords and identity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;EXCLUSIVE&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Insight&lt;/strong&gt; – Improves performance by identifying safe files and only scanning unknown files.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norton Safe Web&lt;/strong&gt; – Proactively protects you while you surf the Web by warning of and blocking unsafe and fake websites right in your search results.&lt;sup&gt;2&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Browser Protection&lt;/strong&gt; – Proactively protects you by checking for and blocking online threats as your browser loads, to stop online threats before they can do damage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Download Insight 2.0&lt;/strong&gt; – Protects you from dangerous applications before you install them by telling you if they are harmful or unstable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vulnerability Protection&lt;/strong&gt; – Stops cybercriminals from using security holes (vulnerabilities) in applications to sneak threats onto your PC.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;IMPROVED&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bandwidth Management 2.0&lt;/strong&gt; – Automatically adjusts Norton data usage updates when you connect to 3G networks to avoid using up your monthly data allotment or causing overage fees.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;EXCLUSIVE&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norton Pulse Updates&lt;/strong&gt; – Updates your protection every 5 to 15 minutes, without disrupting you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="benefits">
            <value>&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Say goodbye to viruses&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It's okay to blink, because we never do – SONAR technology and live 24x7 Threat Monitoring watch over your PC for any suspicious behavior to quickly identify threats.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Download away – we scan the files you download and eliminate online threats that we find.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep clean your PC – our powerful Threat-Removal Layer targets and scrubs out aggressive, hard-to-remove infections that less sophisticated products often miss. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Harness global power – only Norton can bring you the ultra-fast Network Defense Layer to block a multitude of threats before they can even touch your PC.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protection from the future, available today – our exclusive reputation and behavior antivirus technology are so advanced that they can stop online threats that bad guys haven't even created yet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep out trespassers – Browser Protection blocks unsafe websites that secretly download software that can steal personal information or take over your PC.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Neutralize online identity thieves – it's the only way to shop, surf and visit social networks without worry&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It's easy to stumble into the wrong part of the web – we block &quot;phishing&quot; websites set up to trick you into leaking your passwords, credit card numbers or worse.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Facebook links are tempting – now you don't need to worry if a Facebook News Feed contains dangerous downloads or fraudulent links.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protects your identity by securely storing and automatically entering your user names and passwords.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Help keep kids safe from Internet dangers with Norton Online Family&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Easily connects you to Norton Online Family right from within your Norton Control Center.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lets you know what your kids are up to online by tracking which websites they visit, and allows you to block inappropriate sites.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keeps an eye on your kids’ social network activities and who they’re chatting with online, so you can spot potential dangers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Engineered to go unnoticed – because great protection doesn't get in your way or slow you down&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blazingly fast performance delivers fast browsing and file scanning.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intelligent detection and quiet background operation block threats and won’t overload you with pop-up warnings or restart requests.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;So smart, it scans and runs updates only when you’re not using your PC – with no need to reboot after updates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Everyone's talking cloud. And with our new Cloud-based Norton Management, it’s easy to stay in control&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lets you fix, update, renew or install Norton products on additional PCs without needing to track down the product key or install CD. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works from anywhere over the Internet with a few simple clicks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="shortDesc">
            <value language="en">Advanced Internet and antivirus protection for anywhere you go and anything you do online.</value>
        </attribute>
    </attributes>
    <skus>
        <sku guid="2A1DD831-724C-3091-8CC2-37DD0FFD5612">
            <code>NAV3331Y</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Type">
                    <skuoptionvalue>1year</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-03-01T00:00:00-08:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true">
                <file>software.exe</file>
                <downloadexpiry>0</downloadexpiry>
                <downloadlimit>0</downloadlimit>
            </digitalasset>
            <image>norton-internet-security.png</image>
            <attributes>
                <attribute key="EULA">
                    <value>eula_1.htm</value>
                </attribute>
            </attributes>
        </sku>
        <sku guid="08A2E028-9DB8-2412-B289-447023E7F26F">
            <code>NAV333U</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Type">
                    <skuoptionvalue>Upgrade</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-03-01T00:00:00-08:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true">
                <file>software.exe</file>
                <downloadexpiry>0</downloadexpiry>
                <downloadlimit>0</downloadlimit>
            </digitalasset>
            <image>BX_NIS_Y13_r_r_EN_342.png</image>
            <attributes>
                <attribute key="EULA">
                    <value>eula_1.htm</value>
                </attribute>
            </attributes>
        </sku>
        <sku guid="851EDD59-D909-33A6-277C-B804C3AEFE01">
            <code>NAV3332Y</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Type">
                    <skuoptionvalue>2year</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-03-01T00:00:00-08:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true">
                <file>software.exe</file>
                <downloadexpiry>0</downloadexpiry>
                <downloadlimit>0</downloadlimit>
            </digitalasset>
            <image>BX_NIS_Y13_r_r_EN_342.png</image>
            <attributes>
                <attribute key="EULA">
                    <value>eula_1.htm</value>
                </attribute>
            </attributes>
        </sku>
    </skus>
    <seo>
        <url>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </url>
        <title>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </title>
        <keywords>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </keywords>
        <description>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </description>
    </seo>
</product>

<product>
    <code>va_standard_subscription</code>
    <name>
        <value language="fr"></value>
        <value language="en">Visual Analytics Standard</value>
    </name>
    <type>subscription</type>
    <taxcode>NONE</taxcode>
    <brand>SAS</brand>
    <image>tab1-notebook2.png</image>
    <availability>
        <storevisible>true</storevisible>
        <notsoldseperately>false</notsoldseperately>
        <enabledate>2013-05-06T16:25:00-07:00</enabledate>
        <minorderqty>1</minorderqty>
        <availabilityrule>ALWAYS_AVAILABLE</availabilityrule>
        <orderlimit>0</orderlimit>
    </availability>
    <attributes>
        <attribute key="system_requirements">
            <value>&lt;div class=&quot;subsection specs&quot;&gt;
			&lt;h3&gt;Client Environment&lt;/h3&gt;
			&lt;div&gt;
				&lt;div&gt;
					&lt;h4&gt;Operating Systems&lt;/h4&gt;
					&lt;ul&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Windows (32-bit): Windows XP Professional, Windows Vista, Windows 7&lt;/li&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Windows x64 (64-bit): Windows XP Professional for x64, Windows Vista for x64, Windows 7 for x64&lt;/li&gt;
					&lt;/ul&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div&gt;
					&lt;h4&gt;Browsers&lt;/h4&gt;
					&lt;ul&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;Firefox 3.6 and above&lt;/li&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;Internet Explorer 8 and 9&lt;/li&gt;
					&lt;/ul&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div&gt;
					&lt;h4&gt;Flash Player&lt;/h4&gt;
					&lt;ul&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;Adobe Flash Player 10.3&lt;/li&gt;
					&lt;/ul&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;h3&gt;Server Environment&lt;/h3&gt;
			&lt;div&gt;
				&lt;div&gt;
					&lt;h4&gt;Operating Systems&lt;/h4&gt;
					&lt;ul&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;Red Hat Enterprise Linux 6&lt;/li&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;SuSE Linux Enterprise Server 11&lt;/li&gt;
					&lt;/ul&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div&gt;
					&lt;h4&gt;Hardware&lt;/h4&gt;
					&lt;ul&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;HP and Dell (with preconfigured hardware and software packaging options).&lt;/li&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;Teradata and EMC Greenplum (dedicated database appliances).&lt;/li&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;SAS will also work with customers who want to use hardware from other vendors, including IBM, Cisco and more. Please contact your local SAS software sales representative for information.&lt;/li&gt;
					&lt;/ul&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div&gt;
					&lt;h4&gt;Middle Tier&lt;/h4&gt;
					&lt;ul&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;JBoss Enterprise Application Platform&lt;/li&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;JBoss Community Edition&lt;/li&gt;
					&lt;/ul&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div&gt;
					&lt;h4&gt;Required Software&lt;/h4&gt;
					&lt;ul&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;Additional software may be required, including one &lt;a href=&quot;/software/data-management/access/index.html&quot;&gt;SAS/ACCESS®&lt;/a&gt; interface to a data source.&lt;/li&gt;
					&lt;/ul&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;h3&gt;SAS Mobile BI Client Support&lt;/h3&gt;
			&lt;div&gt;
				&lt;div&gt;
					&lt;h4&gt;iOS&lt;/h4&gt;
					&lt;p&gt;SAS Mobile BI for iPad is a free application for iOS available in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/sas-mobile-bi/id511030524?mt=8&quot;&gt;iTunes App Store&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
					&lt;ul&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;Platform/OS: Apple iOS v6.0 and above&lt;/li&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;Devices: iPad 2, 3, 4 and Mini&lt;/li&gt;
					&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;div&gt;
					&lt;h4&gt;Android&lt;/h4&gt;
					&lt;p&gt;SAS Mobile BI for Android is a free application for Android available from &lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.sas.android.bimobile&amp;amp;feature=search_result#?t=W251bGwsMSwxLDEsImNvbS5zYXMuYW5kcm9pZC5iaW1vYmlsZSJd&quot;&gt;Google Play&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
					&lt;ul&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;Platform/OS: Android v 4.0 and above&lt;/li&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;Devices: Android tablets 10.1&quot; with 4.0&lt;/li&gt;
					&lt;/ul&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="longDesc">
            <value>&lt;div class=&quot;subsection imgleft clearfix&quot;&gt;
			&lt;div class=&quot;img&quot;&gt;
				&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.sas.com/software/visual-analytics/images/dv-1-datavisualizer.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Data transforming into a meaningful visualization&quot;&gt; 
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;div class=&quot;txt&quot;&gt;
				&lt;h2&gt;Get the Picture. Fast.&lt;/h2&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Unlike traditional data visualization tools, SAS Visual Analytics produces blazingly fast insights while letting you interactively explore all relevant data – no subsetting or sampling required. The data is quickly read into memory for fast processing. In just minutes or even seconds, you can apply predictive and descriptive analytics to data of any size to spot previously unknown patterns, identify key relationships and uncover insights that would otherwise stay hidden.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.sas.com/software/visual-analytics/demos/all-demos.html&quot;&gt;Demo: Try it now&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="features">
            <value>&lt;div class=&quot;subsection features&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;feature-img&quot;&gt;
&lt;img id=&quot;fbase&quot; src=&quot;http://www.sas.com/software/visual-analytics/images/features/dv/dv-base.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot of data visualization with SAS Visual Analytics software&quot;&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;illus hidden&quot; id=&quot;f-1-img&quot; src=&quot;http://www.sas.com/software/visual-analytics/images/features/dv/dv-1.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot of 'what does it mean' feature&quot; style=&quot;z-index: 200;&quot;&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;illus hidden&quot; id=&quot;f-2-img&quot; src=&quot;http://www.sas.com/software/visual-analytics/images/features/dv/dv-2.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot of toggle feature for adjusting visualization appearance&quot;&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;illus hidden&quot; id=&quot;f-3-img&quot; src=&quot;http://www.sas.com/software/visual-analytics/images/features/dv/dv-3.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot of dynamic filtering&quot;&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;illus hidden&quot; id=&quot;f-4-img&quot; src=&quot;http://www.sas.com/software/visual-analytics/images/features/dv/dv-4.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot of forecast&quot;&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;feature-list&quot;&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Web-based, interactive data exploration mode suits the needs of all types of users.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Autocharting automatically chooses the graph best suited to display the selected data.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Geographical map views provide a quick understanding of geospatial data.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li class=&quot;illustrated&quot; id=&quot;f-1&quot;&gt;&quot;What does it mean&quot; capabilities automatically identify and explain the relationships between variables. &lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Exploration capabilities are available for in-memory server data sources.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Graphical skins can be applied for 3-D appearance and light effects on visuals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;feature-list&quot;&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Compelling visuals include box plots, heat maps, bubble charts and more.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li class=&quot;illustrated&quot; id=&quot;f-2&quot;&gt;The toggle feature displays grid lines and lets you adjust axes to optimize viewing.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li class=&quot;illustrated&quot; id=&quot;f-3&quot;&gt;Queries can be changed by selecting items to be displayed from a sidebar or by dynamic filtering and grouping.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;A resizable overview bar lets you visually subset a portion of data sets with many records (high cardinality).&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li class=&quot;illustrated&quot; id=&quot;f-4&quot;&gt;New forecasting capabilities help you explore data to find out what might happen in the future.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Thumbnails of recent and favorite items can be viewed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="benefits">
            <value>&lt;div class=&quot;subsection imgleft clearfix&quot;&gt;
			&lt;div class=&quot;img&quot;&gt;
				&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.sas.com/software/visual-analytics/images/dv-1-datavisualizer.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Data transforming into a meaningful visualization&quot;&gt; 
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;div class=&quot;txt&quot;&gt;
				&lt;h2&gt;Get the Picture. Fast.&lt;/h2&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Unlike traditional data visualization tools, SAS Visual Analytics produces blazingly fast insights while letting you interactively explore all relevant data – no subsetting or sampling required. The data is quickly read into memory for fast processing. In just minutes or even seconds, you can apply predictive and descriptive analytics to data of any size to spot previously unknown patterns, identify key relationships and uncover insights that would otherwise stay hidden.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.sas.com/software/visual-analytics/demos/all-demos.html&quot;&gt;Demo: Try it now&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="shortDesc">
            <value language="en">Better data visualization. Easy analytics.  Discover a new world of possibilities.</value>
        </attribute>
    </attributes>
    <skus>
        <sku guid="2F20AB0E-994C-8544-6BEF-46CCF9CF7DA8">
            <code>3seats_perp</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Seats">
                    <skuoptionvalue>3seats</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
                <skuoption code="ContractLength">
                    <skuoptionvalue>perpetuity</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-05-06T00:00:00-07:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true"/>
            <image>tab1-notebook2.png</image>
            <attributes>
                <attribute key="EULA">
                    <value>eula_1.htm</value>
                </attribute>
            </attributes>
        </sku>
        <sku guid="F1332357-943C-9B75-9D85-59A4E0E587E4">
            <code>3seats_1year</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Seats">
                    <skuoptionvalue>3seats</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
                <skuoption code="ContractLength">
                    <skuoptionvalue>1yr</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-05-08T00:00:00-07:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true"/>
            <image>tab1-notebook2.png</image>
            <attributes>
                <attribute key="EULA">
                    <value>eula_1.htm</value>
                </attribute>
            </attributes>
        </sku>
        <sku guid="1934B6F5-757D-927E-29AA-D2D8D585FA62">
            <code>2seats_perp</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Seats">
                    <skuoptionvalue>2seats</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
                <skuoption code="ContractLength">
                    <skuoptionvalue>perpetuity</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-05-06T00:00:00-07:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true"/>
            <image>tab1-notebook2.png</image>
            <attributes>
                <attribute key="EULA">
                    <value>eula_1.htm</value>
                </attribute>
            </attributes>
        </sku>
        <sku guid="789DEB4F-C2E5-9FC3-1320-8CD054C47A06">
            <code>2seats_1year</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Seats">
                    <skuoptionvalue>2seats</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
                <skuoption code="ContractLength">
                    <skuoptionvalue>1yr</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-05-06T00:00:00-07:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true"/>
            <image>tab1-notebook2.png</image>
            <attributes>
                <attribute key="EULA">
                    <value>eula_1.htm</value>
                </attribute>
            </attributes>
        </sku>
        <sku guid="BA14E2B7-3403-B4B0-47F3-A35A36D0DD2C">
            <code>5seats_1year</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Seats">
                    <skuoptionvalue>5seats</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
                <skuoption code="ContractLength">
                    <skuoptionvalue>1yr</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-05-08T00:00:00-07:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true"/>
            <image>tab1-notebook2.png</image>
            <attributes>
                <attribute key="EULA">
                    <value>eula_1.htm</value>
                </attribute>
            </attributes>
        </sku>
        <sku guid="A9E3AFB3-812F-B622-BCD3-5F75BF01D836">
            <code>5seats_perp</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Seats">
                    <skuoptionvalue>5seats</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
                <skuoption code="ContractLength">
                    <skuoptionvalue>perpetuity</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-05-08T00:00:00-07:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true"/>
            <image>tab1-notebook2.png</image>
            <attributes>
                <attribute key="EULA">
                    <value>eula_1.htm</value>
                </attribute>
            </attributes>
        </sku>
        <sku guid="DD4ACC02-44D1-0085-B81C-CE6A8A8106D6">
            <code>1seat_perp</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Seats">
                    <skuoptionvalue>1seat</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
                <skuoption code="ContractLength">
                    <skuoptionvalue>perpetuity</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-05-07T00:00:00-07:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true"/>
            <image>tab1-notebook2.png</image>
            <attributes>
                <attribute key="EULA">
                    <value>eula_1.htm</value>
                </attribute>
            </attributes>
        </sku>
        <sku guid="5D317539-9188-A404-7EC7-5BA9D74BC2B4">
            <code>4seats_perp</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Seats">
                    <skuoptionvalue>4seats</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
                <skuoption code="ContractLength">
                    <skuoptionvalue>perpetuity</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-05-08T00:00:00-07:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true"/>
            <image>tab1-notebook2.png</image>
            <attributes>
                <attribute key="EULA">
                    <value>eula_1.htm</value>
                </attribute>
            </attributes>
        </sku>
        <sku guid="705DFA7E-D927-6462-DA66-886932A7DC7D">
            <code>1seat_1year</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Seats">
                    <skuoptionvalue>1seat</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
                <skuoption code="ContractLength">
                    <skuoptionvalue>1yr</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-05-06T00:00:00-07:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true"/>
            <image>tab1-notebook2.png</image>
            <attributes>
                <attribute key="EULA">
                    <value>eula_1.htm</value>
                </attribute>
            </attributes>
        </sku>
        <sku guid="ABB14C42-6368-DC52-DA8E-80A89A71AFA1">
            <code>4seats_1year</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Seats">
                    <skuoptionvalue>4seats</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
                <skuoption code="ContractLength">
                    <skuoptionvalue>1yr</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-05-05T00:00:00-07:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true"/>
            <image>tab1-notebook2.png</image>
            <attributes>
                <attribute key="EULA">
                    <value>eula_1.htm</value>
                </attribute>
            </attributes>
        </sku>
    </skus>
    <seo>
        <url>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </url>
        <title>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </title>
        <keywords>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </keywords>
        <description>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </description>
    </seo>
</product>

<product>
    <code>va_professional_subscription</code>
    <name>
        <value language="fr"></value>
        <value language="en">Visual Analytics Professional</value>
    </name>
    <type>subscription</type>
    <taxcode>NONE</taxcode>
    <brand>SAS</brand>
    <image>tab1-notebook2.png</image>
    <availability>
        <storevisible>true</storevisible>
        <notsoldseperately>false</notsoldseperately>
        <enabledate>2013-05-07T16:42:00-07:00</enabledate>
        <minorderqty>1</minorderqty>
        <availabilityrule>ALWAYS_AVAILABLE</availabilityrule>
        <orderlimit>0</orderlimit>
    </availability>
    <attributes>
        <attribute key="system_requirements">
            <value>&lt;div class=&quot;subsection specs&quot;&gt;
			&lt;h3&gt;Client Environment&lt;/h3&gt;
			&lt;div&gt;
				&lt;div&gt;
					&lt;h4&gt;Operating Systems&lt;/h4&gt;
					&lt;ul&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Windows (32-bit): Windows XP Professional, Windows Vista, Windows 7&lt;/li&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Windows x64 (64-bit): Windows XP Professional for x64, Windows Vista for x64, Windows 7 for x64&lt;/li&gt;
					&lt;/ul&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div&gt;
					&lt;h4&gt;Browsers&lt;/h4&gt;
					&lt;ul&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;Firefox 3.6 and above&lt;/li&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;Internet Explorer 8 and 9&lt;/li&gt;
					&lt;/ul&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div&gt;
					&lt;h4&gt;Flash Player&lt;/h4&gt;
					&lt;ul&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;Adobe Flash Player 10.3&lt;/li&gt;
					&lt;/ul&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;h3&gt;Server Environment&lt;/h3&gt;
			&lt;div&gt;
				&lt;div&gt;
					&lt;h4&gt;Operating Systems&lt;/h4&gt;
					&lt;ul&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;Red Hat Enterprise Linux 6&lt;/li&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;SuSE Linux Enterprise Server 11&lt;/li&gt;
					&lt;/ul&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div&gt;
					&lt;h4&gt;Hardware&lt;/h4&gt;
					&lt;ul&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;HP and Dell (with preconfigured hardware and software packaging options).&lt;/li&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;Teradata and EMC Greenplum (dedicated database appliances).&lt;/li&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;SAS will also work with customers who want to use hardware from other vendors, including IBM, Cisco and more. Please contact your local SAS software sales representative for information.&lt;/li&gt;
					&lt;/ul&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div&gt;
					&lt;h4&gt;Middle Tier&lt;/h4&gt;
					&lt;ul&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;JBoss Enterprise Application Platform&lt;/li&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;JBoss Community Edition&lt;/li&gt;
					&lt;/ul&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div&gt;
					&lt;h4&gt;Required Software&lt;/h4&gt;
					&lt;ul&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;Additional software may be required, including one &lt;a href=&quot;/software/data-management/access/index.html&quot;&gt;SAS/ACCESS®&lt;/a&gt; interface to a data source.&lt;/li&gt;
					&lt;/ul&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;h3&gt;SAS Mobile BI Client Support&lt;/h3&gt;
			&lt;div&gt;
				&lt;div&gt;
					&lt;h4&gt;iOS&lt;/h4&gt;
					&lt;p&gt;SAS Mobile BI for iPad is a free application for iOS available in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/sas-mobile-bi/id511030524?mt=8&quot;&gt;iTunes App Store&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
					&lt;ul&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;Platform/OS: Apple iOS v6.0 and above&lt;/li&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;Devices: iPad 2, 3, 4 and Mini&lt;/li&gt;
					&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;div&gt;
					&lt;h4&gt;Android&lt;/h4&gt;
					&lt;p&gt;SAS Mobile BI for Android is a free application for Android available from &lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.sas.android.bimobile&amp;amp;feature=search_result#?t=W251bGwsMSwxLDEsImNvbS5zYXMuYW5kcm9pZC5iaW1vYmlsZSJd&quot;&gt;Google Play&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
					&lt;ul&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;Platform/OS: Android v 4.0 and above&lt;/li&gt;
						&lt;li&gt;Devices: Android tablets 10.1&quot; with 4.0&lt;/li&gt;
					&lt;/ul&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="longDesc">
            <value>&lt;div class=&quot;subsection imgleft clearfix&quot;&gt;
			&lt;div class=&quot;img&quot;&gt;
				&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.sas.com/software/visual-analytics/images/dv-1-datavisualizer.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Data transforming into a meaningful visualization&quot;&gt; 
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;div class=&quot;txt&quot;&gt;
				&lt;h2&gt;Get the Picture. Fast.&lt;/h2&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Unlike traditional data visualization tools, SAS Visual Analytics produces blazingly fast insights while letting you interactively explore all relevant data – no subsetting or sampling required. The data is quickly read into memory for fast processing. In just minutes or even seconds, you can apply predictive and descriptive analytics to data of any size to spot previously unknown patterns, identify key relationships and uncover insights that would otherwise stay hidden.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.sas.com/software/visual-analytics/demos/all-demos.html&quot;&gt;Demo: Try it now&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="features">
            <value>&lt;div class=&quot;subsection features&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;feature-img&quot;&gt;
&lt;img id=&quot;fbase&quot; src=&quot;http://www.sas.com/software/visual-analytics/images/features/dv/dv-base.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot of data visualization with SAS Visual Analytics software&quot;&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;illus hidden&quot; id=&quot;f-1-img&quot; src=&quot;http://www.sas.com/software/visual-analytics/images/features/dv/dv-1.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot of 'what does it mean' feature&quot; style=&quot;z-index: 200;&quot;&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;illus hidden&quot; id=&quot;f-2-img&quot; src=&quot;http://www.sas.com/software/visual-analytics/images/features/dv/dv-2.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot of toggle feature for adjusting visualization appearance&quot;&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;illus hidden&quot; id=&quot;f-3-img&quot; src=&quot;http://www.sas.com/software/visual-analytics/images/features/dv/dv-3.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot of dynamic filtering&quot;&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;illus hidden&quot; id=&quot;f-4-img&quot; src=&quot;http://www.sas.com/software/visual-analytics/images/features/dv/dv-4.png&quot; alt=&quot;Screenshot of forecast&quot;&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;feature-list&quot;&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Web-based, interactive data exploration mode suits the needs of all types of users.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Autocharting automatically chooses the graph best suited to display the selected data.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Geographical map views provide a quick understanding of geospatial data.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li class=&quot;illustrated&quot; id=&quot;f-1&quot;&gt;&quot;What does it mean&quot; capabilities automatically identify and explain the relationships between variables. &lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Exploration capabilities are available for in-memory server data sources.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Graphical skins can be applied for 3-D appearance and light effects on visuals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;feature-list&quot;&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Compelling visuals include box plots, heat maps, bubble charts and more.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li class=&quot;illustrated&quot; id=&quot;f-2&quot;&gt;The toggle feature displays grid lines and lets you adjust axes to optimize viewing.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li class=&quot;illustrated&quot; id=&quot;f-3&quot;&gt;Queries can be changed by selecting items to be displayed from a sidebar or by dynamic filtering and grouping.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;A resizable overview bar lets you visually subset a portion of data sets with many records (high cardinality).&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li class=&quot;illustrated&quot; id=&quot;f-4&quot;&gt;New forecasting capabilities help you explore data to find out what might happen in the future.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Thumbnails of recent and favorite items can be viewed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="benefits">
            <value>&lt;div class=&quot;subsection imgleft clearfix&quot;&gt;
			&lt;div class=&quot;img&quot;&gt;
				&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.sas.com/software/visual-analytics/images/dv-1-datavisualizer.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Data transforming into a meaningful visualization&quot;&gt; 
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;div class=&quot;txt&quot;&gt;
				&lt;h2&gt;Get the Picture. Fast.&lt;/h2&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Unlike traditional data visualization tools, SAS Visual Analytics produces blazingly fast insights while letting you interactively explore all relevant data – no subsetting or sampling required. The data is quickly read into memory for fast processing. In just minutes or even seconds, you can apply predictive and descriptive analytics to data of any size to spot previously unknown patterns, identify key relationships and uncover insights that would otherwise stay hidden.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.sas.com/software/visual-analytics/demos/all-demos.html&quot;&gt;Demo: Try it now&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="shortDesc">
            <value language="en">Better data visualization. Easy analytics. Discover a new world of possibilities. Support for metered data usage.</value>
        </attribute>
    </attributes>
    <skus>
        <sku guid="66CA839C-ECCA-1CCD-D0D4-5DEF4CEE70B3">
            <code>va_pro_5seats</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Seats">
                    <skuoptionvalue>5seats</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
                <skuoption code="ContractLength">
                    <skuoptionvalue>perpetuity</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-05-05T00:00:00-07:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true"/>
            <image>tab1-notebook2.png</image>
            <attributes>
                <attribute key="EULA">
                    <value>eula_1.htm</value>
                </attribute>
            </attributes>
        </sku>
        <sku guid="76F7CADD-3688-850E-109E-252901A656B6">
            <code>va_pro_1seat</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Seats">
                    <skuoptionvalue>1seat</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
                <skuoption code="ContractLength">
                    <skuoptionvalue>perpetuity</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-05-07T00:00:00-07:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true"/>
            <image>tab1-notebook2.png</image>
            <attributes>
                <attribute key="EULA">
                    <value>eula_1.htm</value>
                </attribute>
            </attributes>
        </sku>
        <sku guid="632AC711-1818-CDD3-AC79-57B83FAB5810">
            <code>2seats_1year_pro</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Seats">
                    <skuoptionvalue>2seats</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
                <skuoption code="ContractLength">
                    <skuoptionvalue>1yr</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-04-11T00:00:00-07:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true"/>
            <image>tab1-notebook2.png</image>
            <attributes>
                <attribute key="EULA">
                    <value>eula_1.htm</value>
                </attribute>
            </attributes>
        </sku>
        <sku guid="CCD397A3-E211-1926-9A26-6DFE63A49A91">
            <code>3seats_1year_pro</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Seats">
                    <skuoptionvalue>3seats</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
                <skuoption code="ContractLength">
                    <skuoptionvalue>1yr</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-05-06T00:00:00-07:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true"/>
            <image>tab1-notebook2.png</image>
            <attributes>
                <attribute key="EULA">
                    <value>eula_1.htm</value>
                </attribute>
            </attributes>
        </sku>
        <sku guid="516A1D43-8D35-EDFB-44AB-A0CAFEC6C573">
            <code>5seats_1year_pro</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Seats">
                    <skuoptionvalue>5seats</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
                <skuoption code="ContractLength">
                    <skuoptionvalue>1yr</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-05-06T00:00:00-07:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true"/>
            <image>tab1-notebook2.png</image>
            <attributes>
                <attribute key="EULA">
                    <value>eula_1.htm</value>
                </attribute>
            </attributes>
        </sku>
        <sku guid="0A187CCB-A406-4813-F2F7-2418EC83E2E3">
            <code>va_pro_3seats</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Seats">
                    <skuoptionvalue>3seats</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
                <skuoption code="ContractLength">
                    <skuoptionvalue>perpetuity</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-05-08T00:00:00-07:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true"/>
            <image>tab1-notebook2.png</image>
            <attributes>
                <attribute key="EULA">
                    <value>eula_1.htm</value>
                </attribute>
            </attributes>
        </sku>
        <sku guid="6AA4EDCE-A01A-300F-C895-9432343121E5">
            <code>1seat_1year_pro</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Seats">
                    <skuoptionvalue>1seat</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
                <skuoption code="ContractLength">
                    <skuoptionvalue>1yr</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-05-05T00:00:00-07:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true"/>
            <image>tab1-notebook2.png</image>
            <attributes>
                <attribute key="EULA">
                    <value>eula_1.htm</value>
                </attribute>
            </attributes>
        </sku>
        <sku guid="F488AF8A-B7AA-AA9F-29BD-CEEEACFB6674">
            <code>va_pro_2seats</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Seats">
                    <skuoptionvalue>2seats</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
                <skuoption code="ContractLength">
                    <skuoptionvalue>perpetuity</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-05-05T00:00:00-07:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true"/>
            <image>tab1-notebook2.png</image>
            <attributes>
                <attribute key="EULA">
                    <value>eula_1.htm</value>
                </attribute>
            </attributes>
        </sku>
        <sku guid="CF475379-5125-8BFB-51E2-42C4BD89EA84">
            <code>va_pro_4seats</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Seats">
                    <skuoptionvalue>4seats</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
                <skuoption code="ContractLength">
                    <skuoptionvalue>perpetuity</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-05-08T00:00:00-07:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true"/>
            <image>tab1-notebook2.png</image>
            <attributes>
                <attribute key="EULA">
                    <value>eula_1.htm</value>
                </attribute>
            </attributes>
        </sku>
        <sku guid="86E5BF33-D477-F276-539F-D5696653C7F3">
            <code>4seats_1year_pro</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Seats">
                    <skuoptionvalue>4seats</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
                <skuoption code="ContractLength">
                    <skuoptionvalue>1yr</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-05-05T00:00:00-07:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true"/>
            <image>tab1-notebook2.png</image>
            <attributes>
                <attribute key="EULA">
                    <value>eula_1.htm</value>
                </attribute>
            </attributes>
        </sku>
    </skus>
    <seo>
        <url>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </url>
        <title>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </title>
        <keywords>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </keywords>
        <description>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </description>
    </seo>
</product>

<product>
    <code>NAT231</code>
    <name>
        <value language="fr"></value>
        <value language="en">Norton™ Anti-Theft</value>
    </name>
    <type>product</type>
    <taxcode>GOODS</taxcode>
    <brand>Symantec</brand>
    <image>blank-box.png</image>
    <availability>
        <storevisible>true</storevisible>
        <notsoldseperately>false</notsoldseperately>
        <enabledate>2013-10-01T15:20:00-07:00</enabledate>
        <minorderqty>1</minorderqty>
        <availabilityrule>AVAILABLE_FOR_PRE_ORDER</availabilityrule>
        <orderlimit>0</orderlimit>
        <expectedreleasedate>2014-10-31T00:00:00-07:00</expectedreleasedate>
    </availability>
    <attributes>
        <attribute key="longDesc">
            <value>&lt;p&gt;A simple online control console lists protected devices and offers detailed information about the selected device. The Find Device tab displays recent locations on a map, along with a time stamp and an estimated address. For Android devices with built-in GPS this can be quite accurate. Few laptops come with GPS built in, but virtually all have WiFi. In my testing, WiFi triangulation located the laptop within a few hundred feet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like Snuko Anti-Theft &amp; Data Recovery Premium ($29.95/year direct, 2.5 stars), Norton Anti-Theft can use server-based geolocation when WiFi isn’t available. LoJack for Laptops by Absolute Software ($39.99/year direct, 4.5 stars) makes server-based geolocation its default, reserving the more accurate WiFi triangulation for the premium edition and for the company's recovery agents who take over when the device is reported stolen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Server-based geolocation can range from moderately to wildly inaccurate. It located one of my test systems in a swampy field about eight miles away. Another seemed to be in New York, because I logged in through PCMag's Virtual Private Network. Luckily the most portable devices are the most likely to incorporate better location technology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By default, Norton Anti-Theft makes a location check once per hour, though you can set it to wait as much as 24 hours between checks. When you report the device lost it switches to checking every five minutes.&lt;/p&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="shortDesc">
            <value language="en">Never lose track of your digital devices with Norton™ Anti-Theft.</value>
        </attribute>
    </attributes>
    <skus>
        <sku guid="68fb87a3-f46f-4377-acc8-72f9c2e1ca68">
            <code>NATYR1</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Type">
                    <skuoptionvalue>1pc</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-10-15T00:00:00-07:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true"/>
            <image>blank-box.png</image>
            <attributes/>
        </sku>
    </skus>
    <seo>
        <url>
            <value language="fr"/>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </url>
        <title>
            <value language="fr"/>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </title>
        <keywords>
            <value language="fr"/>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </keywords>
        <description>
            <value language="fr"/>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </description>
    </seo>
</product>

<product>
    <code>NIS983</code>
    <name>
        <value language="fr"></value>
        <value language="en">Norton™ Security for Mac</value>
    </name>
    <type>product</type>
    <taxcode>GOODS</taxcode>
    <brand>Symantec</brand>
    <image>norton-internet-security.png</image>
    <availability>
        <storevisible>true</storevisible>
        <notsoldseperately>false</notsoldseperately>
        <enabledate>2013-03-01T18:23:00-08:00</enabledate>
        <minorderqty>1</minorderqty>
        <availabilityrule>AVAILABLE_WHEN_IN_STOCK</availabilityrule>
        <orderlimit>0</orderlimit>
    </availability>
    <attributes>
        <attribute key="longDesc">
            <value>&lt;p&gt;Norton Internet Security, developed by Symantec Corporation, is a computer program that provides malware prevention and removal during subscription period and uses signatures and heuristics to identify viruses. Other features include a personal firewall, email spam filtering, and phishing protection. Symantec distributes the product as a download, a boxed copy, and as OEM software. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Norton Internet Security held a 61% market share in the United States retail security suite category in the first half of 2007. In this study, competitors, in terms of market share, included security suites from CA, Inc., Trend Micro, and Kaspersky Lab.&lt;/p&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="shortDesc">
            <value language="en">Advanced protection to surf, bank and shop online with your Mac.</value>
        </attribute>
    </attributes>
    <skus>
        <sku guid="3bdea46b-27e2-4553-9ebd-0ec47ac61ebc">
            <code>NIS1YR</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Type">
                    <skuoptionvalue>1year</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-09-01T00:00:00-07:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true"/>
            <image>norton-internet-security.png</image>
            <attributes/>
        </sku>
    </skus>
    <seo>
        <url>
            <value language="fr"/>
            <value language="en"/>
        </url>
        <title>
            <value language="fr"/>
            <value language="en"/>
        </title>
        <keywords>
            <value language="fr"/>
            <value language="en"/>
        </keywords>
        <description>
            <value language="fr"/>
            <value language="en"/>
        </description>
    </seo>
</product>

<product>
    <code>NGH112</code>
    <name>
        <value language="fr"></value>
        <value language="en">Norton Ghost 16</value>
    </name>
    <type>product</type>
    <taxcode>GOODS</taxcode>
    <brand>Symantec</brand>
    <image>norton-ghost.png</image>
    <availability>
        <storevisible>true</storevisible>
        <notsoldseperately>false</notsoldseperately>
        <enabledate>2013-03-01T17:11:00-08:00</enabledate>
        <minorderqty>1</minorderqty>
        <availabilityrule>ALWAYS_AVAILABLE</availabilityrule>
        <orderlimit>0</orderlimit>
    </availability>
    <attributes>
        <attribute key="system_requirements">
            <value>&lt;h3&gt;Windows® 7 Starter/Home Basic/Home Premium/Professional/Enterprise/Ultimate&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must meet minimum Windows 7 operating system requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Windows Vista® Home Basic/Home Premium/Business/Ultimate&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must meet minimum Windows Vista operating system requirements &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 class=&quot;cbMrgnBtmMD&quot;&gt;Windows® XP Home/Professional&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;300 MHz or faster processor&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;512 MB (1GB recommended) of RAM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;430 MB of available hard disk space&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CD-ROM or DVD-ROM drive for software distribution on media&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Super VGA (800 x 600) or higher resolution video adapter and monitor&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Windows® 8&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not ready for Windows 8&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Supported File Systems and Devices&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;FAT16, FAT16X, FAT32, FAT32X&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NTFS, GUID Partition Table (GPT)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dynamic Disks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Supported Hard Drives and Removable Media&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CDR/RW, DVD+-R/RW, Blu-Ray devices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;USB and FireWire® (IEEE 1394) devices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Iomega® Zip® and Jaz® drives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="longDesc">
            <value>&lt;div class=&quot;PD-copy&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Protect your applications, settings, folders, and files with professional grade backup and recovery.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provides powerful control over full system and file backups&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Restores from system failures &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Backs up on schedules and events&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Saves recovery points to offsite locations including FTP &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
	
&lt;div class=&quot;mod centered topPadding&quot; style=&quot;margin-left: 0; text-align: left;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="features">
            <value>&lt;div class=&quot;mod&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NEW! Cold Imaging&lt;/strong&gt; lets you back up files without installing Ghost.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NEW! Blu-ray Disc&lt;/strong&gt; allows you to back up large amounts of data to high-capacity Blu-ray Disc — up to 25 GB per disc (50 GB dual-layer).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NEW! Windows® 7 support&lt;/strong&gt; including support for Bitlocker™ provides enhanced data protection through drive encryption and integrity checking.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NEW! Symantec ThreatCon integration&lt;/strong&gt; leverages intelligence from Symantec’s industry-leading security research organization to automatically backup files whenever ThreatCon reaches a specified threat level.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Full system (disk image) backup&lt;/strong&gt; lets you easily back up everything on a hard drive or partition.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;File and folder backup&lt;/strong&gt; lets you back up only the files and folders you choose, rather than saving an entire drive.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;File backup search&lt;/strong&gt; finds and backs up only the types of files you choose, such as photos, MP3 files, and documents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incremental backup&lt;/strong&gt; copies only files that have changed for fewer, faster backups.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Customizable, event-based backup&lt;/strong&gt; triggers backups based on key events such as when you install a new program or when there are sudden increases in data storage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Offsite backup&lt;/strong&gt; copies recovery points to a FTP site for easier offsite backup management.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NAS backup&lt;/strong&gt; gives you the option of backing up your files to network-attached storage devices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advanced compression&lt;/strong&gt; automatically compresses files so you can store more files in less space.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advanced encryption&lt;/strong&gt; helps keep your sensitive documents safe from prying eyes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;System protection&lt;/strong&gt; lets you easily restore your system, applications and files even when you can’t restart the operating system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Google Desktop™ integration&lt;/strong&gt; makes data recovery even faster with searchable backup indexes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LightsOut Restore&lt;/strong&gt; lets you quickly restore your system without needing a bootable CD.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Remote management&lt;/strong&gt; lets you remotely control other Norton Ghost installations (12.0 and higher) on your local area network.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scheduled P2V&lt;/strong&gt; allows you to automatically create a virtual disk from your most recent backup.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Version support&lt;/strong&gt; lets you restore older disk images made with Ghost 10, 12 and 14.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Throttle control&lt;/strong&gt; allows backups to occur seamlessly in the background while you’re using your PC.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;File compression and password-encryption&lt;/strong&gt; ensure fast, efficient, secure backups.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;At-a-glance system status&lt;/strong&gt; displays all scheduled backups and the degree of backup protection for each computer drive, all in one view.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multiple storage options&lt;/strong&gt; let you back up to almost any media, including Blu-ray Disc®, CDR/RW and DVD+-R/RW drives, USB and FireWire® (IEEE 1394) devices, network drives, and Iomega® Zip® and Jaz® drives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="benefits">
            <value>&lt;div class=&quot;mod&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul id=&quot;accordianTab1&quot; class=&quot;listContent&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Automatically backup your files, photos and more&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Safeguards your photos, videos, music and other files with automatic backup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Takes periodic snapshots of your entire computer hard drive to be able to completely restore your computer system to a specific backup version in the case of hard drive failure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Automatically backs up when online threats raise an increased need to save the latest version of your system&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Convenient access for recovery&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lets you back up to and recover your files from a CD, DVD, Blu-ray Disc™, external drive or a networked attached storage (NAS) device&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provides easy recovery of your data files, or your entire hard drive or a mapped drive to a previous backup image&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Allows you to quickly restore your system without needing a bootable CD&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Thoughtful management&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compresses disk images to store your backups in less space&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Encrypts your backups to keep your data safe from prying eyes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lets you remotely control other Norton Ghost installations (version 12.0 and higher) on your local area network&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="shortDesc">
            <value language="en">Protect your applications, settings, folders, and files with professional grade backup and recovery.</value>
        </attribute>
    </attributes>
    <skus>
        <sku guid="6B97EFB5-4E07-8054-C14B-93EB236F7645">
            <code>NGH1121PC</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Type">
                    <skuoptionvalue>1pc</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-03-01T00:00:00-08:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true">
                <file>software.exe</file>
                <downloadexpiry>0</downloadexpiry>
                <downloadlimit>0</downloadlimit>
            </digitalasset>
            <image>norton-ghost.png</image>
            <attributes>
                <attribute key="EULA">
                    <value>eula_2.htm</value>
                </attribute>
            </attributes>
        </sku>
    </skus>
    <seo>
        <url>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </url>
        <title>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </title>
        <keywords>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </keywords>
        <description>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </description>
    </seo>
</product>

<product>
    <code>NAV444TR</code>
    <name>
        <value language="fr"></value>
        <value language="en">Norton Utilities™ 30-Day Trial</value>
    </name>
    <type>trial</type>
    <taxcode>GOODS</taxcode>
    <brand>Symantec</brand>
    <image>norton-utilities.png</image>
    <availability>
        <storevisible>true</storevisible>
        <notsoldseperately>false</notsoldseperately>
        <enabledate>2013-03-05T17:30:00-08:00</enabledate>
        <minorderqty>1</minorderqty>
        <availabilityrule>ALWAYS_AVAILABLE</availabilityrule>
        <orderlimit>0</orderlimit>
    </availability>
    <attributes>
        <attribute key="system_requirements">
            <value>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Microsoft® Windows® XP SP3 (32-bit only)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CPU: Pentium® or equivalent 233 MHz (minimum) | Pentium or equivalent 300 MHz (recommended)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Memory: 64 MB (minimum) | 128 MB (recommended)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Microsoft Windows Vista® (32-bit and 64-bit)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CPU: 1 GHz&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Memory: 1 GB&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Microsoft Windows 7 and Microsoft Windows 8&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CPU: 1 GHz&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Memory: 1 GB for 32-bit | 2 GB for 64-bit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Additional Hardware Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100 MB of available hard disk space &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SVGA (1024 x 768) video&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CD-ROM or DVD drive (if not installing via electronic software download)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Internet connection (to activate product and receive product updates)&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt; User is responsible for Internet service provider account, all Internet access fees, and phone charges.&lt;/p&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="features">
            <value>&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Duplicate File Finder&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; Finds all of the duplicate files scattered across your computer's hard drive, so you can remove them and free up disk space for more of your Stuff.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;System Dashboard&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; Shows you step-by-step how to get your computer to run like new again.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Application Uninstaller&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; Removes the programs you don't use or which take up too many resources.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Speed Disk&amp;trade;&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; Brings together (defragments) and reorganizes (optimizes) files and data that have become scattered across your hard drive.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disk Doctor&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; Scans your hard drive and alerts you to problems that can cause computer errors and crash your hard drive.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disk Cleaner&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; Permanently erases all record of your computer and Web activities to protect your privacy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Registry Cleaner&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; Helps eliminate Windows Registry problems that can slow down your PC, trigger error messages and cause Windows to crash.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Registry Defragmenter&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; Removes gaps, free space and corrupt files in your registry and compacts it to free up system memory and make your PC start up faster.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Registry Restore&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; Makes a backup of the registry before making any repairs so you can easily undo them if necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Startup Manager&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; Lets you choose what programs load automatically when Windows starts in order to free up memory and improve PC startup time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service Manager&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; Improves startup time and reclaims system memory by letting you turn off unneeded system applications (also known as Windows services) that Windows automatically runs in the background.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UnErase&amp;trade; Wizard&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; Lets you quickly restore accidentally deleted files that may still be retrievable on your hard drive.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Smart Updates&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; Silently and automatically installs product upgrades.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="longDesc">
            <value>&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helps your old PC run like new. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Speeds PC startup.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixes common PC problems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Repairs hard drive problems and frees up hard drive space.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="benefits">
            <value>&lt;ul class=&quot;listContent&quot; id=&quot;accordianTab1&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fixes common PC problems and helps keep your computer running fast and trouble-free &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Finds and fixes issues in Microsoft&amp;reg; Windows&amp;reg; to prevent PC freezes, crashes and slow downs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scans for potential problems that can cause your hard drive to crash.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helps you &quot;rescue&quot; accidentally deleted or damaged files that may still be retrievable on your hard drive.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Boosts your PC's performance and helps it run like new again&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lets you turn off services and programs Windows automatically loads at startup, so your PC gets up and running faster.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Safely defragments, repairs and optimizes your Windows registry to help programs load faster and boost overall PC performance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Frees up PC memory, so you can run more programs simultaneously, without slow downs or crashes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cleans up your hard drive to help it run faster and give you more room for your Stuff&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reorganizes (optimizes) files that are scattered across your hard drive, so your PC can find them faster.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Finds all the duplicate files, so you can remove them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Removes the programs you don't use.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Keeps your online activity private and helps prevent your personal information from being stolen&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Permanently erases all record of your Web activities, so others can't see what you do online.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lets you completely and permanently erase old, unwanted and unneeded personal Stuff, so no one can access or retrieve it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="shortDesc">
            <value language="en">&lt;li&gt;Speeds PC startup.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixes common PC problems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Repairs hard drive problems and frees up hard drive space.&lt;/li&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
    </attributes>
    <skus>
        <sku guid="03146CB1-AC2A-CAC9-B91A-3B6E98DB7C62">
            <code>NAV444TR</code>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true">
                <file>software.exe</file>
                <downloadexpiry>0</downloadexpiry>
                <downloadlimit>0</downloadlimit>
            </digitalasset>
        </sku>
    </skus>
    <seo>
        <url>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </url>
        <title>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </title>
        <keywords>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </keywords>
        <description>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </description>
    </seo>
</product>

<product>
    <code>N360</code>
    <name>
        <value language="fr"></value>
        <value language="en">Norton 360™</value>
    </name>
    <type>product</type>
    <taxcode>GOODS</taxcode>
    <brand>Symantec</brand>
    <image>norton-360.png</image>
    <availability>
        <storevisible>true</storevisible>
        <notsoldseperately>false</notsoldseperately>
        <enabledate>2013-03-01T17:34:00-08:00</enabledate>
        <minorderqty>1</minorderqty>
        <availabilityrule>ALWAYS_AVAILABLE</availabilityrule>
        <orderlimit>0</orderlimit>
    </availability>
    <attributes>
        <attribute key="system_requirements">
            <value>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Operating Systems Supported&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft® Windows® XP (32-bit) Home/Professional/Tablet PC/Media Center (32-bit) with Service Pack 2 or later&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Windows Vista® (32-bit and 64-bit) Starter/Home Basic/Home Premium/Business/Ultimate with Service Pack 1 or later&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Windows 7 (32-bit and 64-bit) Starter/Home Basic/Home Premium/Professional/Ultimate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Windows 8 and Windows 8 Pro (32-bit and 64-bit)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum Hardware Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;300 MHz for Microsoft Windows XP, 1 GHz for Microsoft Windows Vista/Microsoft Windows 7/Windows 8&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;256 MB of RAM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;300 MB of available hard disk space&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CD-ROM or DVD drive (if not installing via electronic download)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Browser Support for Phishing Protection, Safe Search, and Password Management&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot; style=&quot;margin-bottom: 3px;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Internet Explorer® 7.0 or higher (32-bit only)&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mozilla® Firefox® (32-bit only)&lt;sup&gt;1,2&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Google Chrome™&lt;sup&gt;1,2&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Browser Support for Vulnerability Protection&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot; style=&quot;margin-bottom: 3px;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Internet Explorer® 7.0 or higher (32-bit only)&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mozilla® Firefox® (32-bit only)&lt;sup&gt;1,2&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support for Antispam&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Outlook® 2002 or later&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Outlook Express 6.0 or later&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Windows Mail (spam filtering only)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="bannerName">
            <value language="en">norton-360-banner.png</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="longDesc">
            <value>&lt;p&gt;Our ultimate Internet and antivirus protection for all you do online&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provides proactive protection, so you can do what you want online, knowing you’re protected.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ultra-fast Internet detection layer stops most threats before they can even reach your computer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Powerful threat-removal layer targets and eliminates even the hardest to remove infections. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="features">
            <value>&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;FEATURES&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our ultimate protection for your PC&lt;/strong&gt; – includes everything from Norton™ AntiVirus and Norton™ Internet Security with 2 GB of secured online storage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;EXCLUSIVE&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norton&lt;/strong&gt;™&lt;strong&gt; Protection System&lt;/strong&gt; – Our 5 patented layers of protection detect and eliminate threats more quickly and accurately than other technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Network Defense Layer Protection&lt;/strong&gt; – Stops online threats before they can reach your computer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;IMPROVED&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SONAR Behavioral Protection &amp;amp; Live 24x7 Threat Monitoring &lt;/strong&gt;– Stays ahead of, detects and eliminates threats that haven’t been invented yet by watching your PC for suspicious activity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;NEW&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Threat-removal Layer &lt;/strong&gt;– Targets and eliminates hard-to-remove threats less sophisticated products often miss.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;EXCLUSIVE&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norton&lt;/strong&gt;™ &lt;strong&gt;Management&lt;/strong&gt; – Cloud-based controls let you fix, update, renew and install Norton 360™ over the Internet with a few simple clicks. It brings together your available Norton™ protection for other devices, like your Mac® computer, smartphone or tablet, in one place.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norton&lt;/strong&gt;™&lt;strong&gt; Safe Web for Facebook &lt;/strong&gt;– Scans your Facebook News Feed for dangerous links, infected downloads and unsafe websites.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Automatic Backup &lt;/strong&gt;– Backs up your photos, music and other important files only when you’re not using your computer, so it won’t get in your way and you don’t have to remember to do it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PC Tuneup&lt;/strong&gt; – Fixes common computer problems, frees up memory, removes unnecessary files and cleans up your hard drive.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;NEW&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Always up-to-date Product Version&lt;/strong&gt; – Norton™ automatically sends you important product and feature updates throughout the year. The latest version installs without you needing to do anything.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FREE 24x7 Support&lt;/strong&gt; – Offers you expert help and answers by phone, live chat or online, whenever you need them. &lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;EXCLUSIVE&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Parental Controls Management&lt;/strong&gt; – Lets you access Norton™ Online Family through Norton 360™.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Antiphishing Technology&lt;/strong&gt; – Blocks fraudulent “phishing” websites set up by online scammers to steal your money, passwords, and identity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norton&lt;/strong&gt;™&lt;strong&gt; Identity Safe &lt;/strong&gt;– Remembers, secures and automatically enters your user names and passwords for you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;EXCLUSIVE&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Insight&lt;/strong&gt; – Improves performance by identifying safe files and only scanning unknown files.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norton&lt;/strong&gt;™&lt;strong&gt; Safe Web&lt;/strong&gt; – Proactively protects you while you surf the Web by warning of and blocking unsafe and fake websites right in your search results.&lt;sup&gt;2&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Browser Protection&lt;/strong&gt; – Proactively protects you by checking for and blocking online threats as your browser loads, to stop online threats before they can do damage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Web-Based Backup Access&lt;/strong&gt; – - Lets you download and share photos, videos and other files you’ve backed up online, anytime, anywhere via the cloud.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Download Insight 2.0&lt;/strong&gt; – Protects you from dangerous applications before you install them by telling you if they are harmful or unstable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vulnerability Protection&lt;/strong&gt; – Stops cybercriminals from using security holes (vulnerabilities) in applications to sneak threats onto your PC.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;IMPROVED&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bandwidth Management 2.0&lt;/strong&gt; – Automatically adjusts Norton™ data usage updates when you connect to 3G networks to avoid using up your monthly data allotment or causing overage fees.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;EXCLUSIVE&lt;/h3&gt; 
&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top: 0;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Norton&lt;/strong&gt;™&lt;strong&gt; Pulse Updates&lt;/strong&gt; – Updates your protection every 5 to 15 minutes, without disrupting you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="benefits">
            <value>&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Say goodbye to viruses&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It's okay to blink, because we never do – SONAR technology and live 24x7 Threat Monitoring watch over your PC for any suspicious behavior to quickly identify threats.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Download away – we scan the files you download and eliminate online threats that we find.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep clean your PC – our powerful Threat-Removal Layer targets and scrubs out aggressive, hard-to-remove infections that less sophisticated products often miss. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Harness global power – only Norton™ can bring you the ultra-fast Network Defense Layer to block a multitude of threats before they can even touch your PC.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protection from the future, available today – our exclusive reputation and behavior antivirus technology are so advanced that they can stop online threats that bad guys haven't even created yet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep out trespassers – Browser Protection blocks unsafe websites that secretly download software that can steal personal information or take over your PC.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Neutralize online identity thieves – it's the only way to shop, surf and visit social networks without worry&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It's easy to stumble into the wrong part of the web – we block &quot;phishing&quot; websites set up to trick you into leaking your passwords, credit card numbers or worse.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Facebook links are tempting – now you don't need to worry if a Facebook News Feed contains dangerous downloads or fraudulent links.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protects your identity by securely storing and automatically entering your user names and passwords.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Help keep kids safe from Internet dangers with Norton&lt;/strong&gt;™&lt;strong&gt; Online Family&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Easily connects you to Norton™ Online Family right from within your Norton™ Control Center.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lets you know what your kids are up to online by tracking which websites they visit, and allows you to block inappropriate sites.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keeps an eye on your kids’ social network activities and who they’re chatting with online, so you can spot potential dangers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Engineered to go unnoticed – because great protection doesn't get in your way or slow you down&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blazingly fast performance delivers fast browsing and file scanning.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intelligent detection and quiet background operation block threats and won’t overload you with pop-up warnings or restart requests.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;So smart, it scans and runs updates only when you’re not using your PC – with no need to reboot after updates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Everyone's talking cloud. And with our new Cloud-based Norton&lt;/strong&gt;™&lt;strong&gt; Management, it’s easy to stay in control&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lets you fix, update, renew or install Norton™ products on additional PCs without needing to track down the product key or install CD. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Works from anywhere over the Internet with a few simple clicks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accidents happen. Hard drives fail. Coffee gets spilled. Make sure you always have a backup.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Automatic backup takes care of your photos, music, and other important files and backs them up to a disc, USB device, or online to one of our secure data centers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Protects files you back up online with government-grade encryption.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lets you get up and running fast - Norton™ backup restores files with just a few clicks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PC need a pick me up? Keep it running fast and trouble-free with our exclusive clean up and tuneup features.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixes common problems that can slow down or cause your PC to crash or freeze.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gets rid of unnecessary files and optimizes your hard drive.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Frees up system memory.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="shortDesc">
            <value language="en">Our ultimate Internet and antivirus protection for all you do online.  Introducing the new Norton 360™.</value>
        </attribute>
    </attributes>
    <skus>
        <sku guid="79791219-A3A7-05CA-AF0B-A62D8399E46D">
            <code>N2601YR</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Type">
                    <skuoptionvalue>1year</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-03-01T00:00:00-08:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true">
                <file>software.exe</file>
                <downloadexpiry>0</downloadexpiry>
                <downloadlimit>0</downloadlimit>
            </digitalasset>
            <image>norton-360.png</image>
            <attributes>
                <attribute key="EULA">
                    <value>eula_1.htm</value>
                </attribute>
            </attributes>
        </sku>
        <sku guid="00FC533B-7641-3CB6-2264-D5EAD3F38A23">
            <code>N360U</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Type">
                    <skuoptionvalue>Upgrade</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-03-01T00:00:00-08:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true">
                <file>software.exe</file>
                <downloadexpiry>0</downloadexpiry>
                <downloadlimit>0</downloadlimit>
            </digitalasset>
            <image>BX_N360_Y13_r_r_EN_342.png</image>
            <attributes>
                <attribute key="EULA">
                    <value>eula_1.htm</value>
                </attribute>
            </attributes>
        </sku>
        <sku guid="0E48341C-01E4-C0AF-A35E-0AEFC9EF2214">
            <code>N3602YR</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Type">
                    <skuoptionvalue>2year</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-03-01T00:00:00-08:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true">
                <file>software.exe</file>
                <downloadexpiry>0</downloadexpiry>
                <downloadlimit>0</downloadlimit>
            </digitalasset>
            <image>BX_N360_Y13_r_r_EN_342.png</image>
            <attributes>
                <attribute key="EULA">
                    <value>eula_1.htm</value>
                </attribute>
            </attributes>
        </sku>
    </skus>
    <seo>
        <url>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </url>
        <title>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </title>
        <keywords>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </keywords>
        <description>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </description>
    </seo>
</product>

<product>
    <code>NAV444</code>
    <name>
        <value language="fr"></value>
        <value language="en">Norton Utilities™</value>
    </name>
    <type>product</type>
    <taxcode>GOODS</taxcode>
    <brand>Symantec</brand>
    <image>norton-utilities.png</image>
    <availability>
        <storevisible>true</storevisible>
        <notsoldseperately>false</notsoldseperately>
        <enabledate>2013-03-01T17:50:00-08:00</enabledate>
        <minorderqty>1</minorderqty>
        <availabilityrule>ALWAYS_AVAILABLE</availabilityrule>
        <orderlimit>0</orderlimit>
    </availability>
    <attributes>
        <attribute key="system_requirements">
            <value>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Microsoft® Windows® XP SP3 (32-bit only)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CPU: Pentium® or equivalent 233 MHz (minimum) | Pentium or equivalent 300 MHz (recommended)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Memory: 64 MB (minimum) | 128 MB (recommended)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Microsoft Windows Vista® (32-bit and 64-bit)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CPU: 1 GHz&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Memory: 1 GB&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Microsoft Windows 7 and Microsoft Windows 8&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CPU: 1 GHz&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Memory: 1 GB for 32-bit | 2 GB for 64-bit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Additional Hardware Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100 MB of available hard disk space &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SVGA (1024 x 768) video&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CD-ROM or DVD drive (if not installing via electronic software download)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Internet connection (to activate product and receive product updates)&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt; User is responsible for Internet service provider account, all Internet access fees, and phone charges.&lt;/p&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="longDesc">
            <value>&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helps your old PC run like new. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Speeds PC startup.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixes common PC problems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Repairs hard drive problems and frees up hard drive space.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="features">
            <value>&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Duplicate File Finder&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; Finds all of the duplicate files scattered across your computer's hard drive, so you can remove them and free up disk space for more of your Stuff.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;System Dashboard&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; Shows you step-by-step how to get your computer to run like new again.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Application Uninstaller&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; Removes the programs you don't use or which take up too many resources.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Speed Disk&amp;trade;&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; Brings together (defragments) and reorganizes (optimizes) files and data that have become scattered across your hard drive.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disk Doctor&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; Scans your hard drive and alerts you to problems that can cause computer errors and crash your hard drive.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disk Cleaner&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; Permanently erases all record of your computer and Web activities to protect your privacy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Registry Cleaner&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; Helps eliminate Windows Registry problems that can slow down your PC, trigger error messages and cause Windows to crash.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Registry Defragmenter&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; Removes gaps, free space and corrupt files in your registry and compacts it to free up system memory and make your PC start up faster.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Registry Restore&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; Makes a backup of the registry before making any repairs so you can easily undo them if necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Startup Manager&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; Lets you choose what programs load automatically when Windows starts in order to free up memory and improve PC startup time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service Manager&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; Improves startup time and reclaims system memory by letting you turn off unneeded system applications (also known as Windows services) that Windows automatically runs in the background.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UnErase&amp;trade; Wizard&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; Lets you quickly restore accidentally deleted files that may still be retrievable on your hard drive.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Smart Updates&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;ndash; Silently and automatically installs product upgrades.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="benefits">
            <value>&lt;ul class=&quot;listContent&quot; id=&quot;accordianTab1&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fixes common PC problems and helps keep your computer running fast and trouble-free &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Finds and fixes issues in Microsoft&amp;reg; Windows&amp;reg; to prevent PC freezes, crashes and slow downs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scans for potential problems that can cause your hard drive to crash.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helps you &quot;rescue&quot; accidentally deleted or damaged files that may still be retrievable on your hard drive.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Boosts your PC's performance and helps it run like new again&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lets you turn off services and programs Windows automatically loads at startup, so your PC gets up and running faster.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Safely defragments, repairs and optimizes your Windows registry to help programs load faster and boost overall PC performance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Frees up PC memory, so you can run more programs simultaneously, without slow downs or crashes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cleans up your hard drive to help it run faster and give you more room for your Stuff&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reorganizes (optimizes) files that are scattered across your hard drive, so your PC can find them faster.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Finds all the duplicate files, so you can remove them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Removes the programs you don't use.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Keeps your online activity private and helps prevent your personal information from being stolen&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Permanently erases all record of your Web activities, so others can't see what you do online.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lets you completely and permanently erase old, unwanted and unneeded personal Stuff, so no one can access or retrieve it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="shortDesc">
            <value language="en">&lt;li&gt;Speeds PC startup.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixes common PC problems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Repairs hard drive problems and frees up hard drive space.&lt;/li&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
    </attributes>
    <skus>
        <sku guid="9F3467BF-5FD1-3220-9E1E-8CA38286EFD4">
            <code>NAV4443P</code>
            <skuoptions>
                <skuoption code="Type">
                    <skuoptionvalue>3pc</skuoptionvalue>
                </skuoption>
            </skuoptions>
            <availability>
                <enabledate>2013-03-01T00:00:00-08:00</enabledate>
            </availability>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true">
                <file>software.exe</file>
                <downloadexpiry>0</downloadexpiry>
                <downloadlimit>0</downloadlimit>
            </digitalasset>
            <image>norton-utilities.png</image>
            <attributes>
                <attribute key="EULA">
                    <value>eula_1.htm</value>
                </attribute>
            </attributes>
        </sku>
    </skus>
    <seo>
        <url>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </url>
        <title>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </title>
        <keywords>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </keywords>
        <description>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </description>
    </seo>
</product>

<product>
    <code>NGH112TR</code>
    <name>
        <value language="fr"></value>
        <value language="en">Norton Ghost™ v16. 30 Day Trial</value>
    </name>
    <type>trial</type>
    <taxcode>GOODS</taxcode>
    <brand>Symantec</brand>
    <image>norton-ghost.png</image>
    <availability>
        <storevisible>true</storevisible>
        <notsoldseperately>false</notsoldseperately>
        <enabledate>2013-03-05T17:53:00-08:00</enabledate>
        <minorderqty>1</minorderqty>
        <availabilityrule>ALWAYS_AVAILABLE</availabilityrule>
        <orderlimit>0</orderlimit>
    </availability>
    <attributes>
        <attribute key="system_requirements">
            <value>&lt;h3&gt;Windows® 7 Starter/Home Basic/Home Premium/Professional/Enterprise/Ultimate&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must meet minimum Windows 7 operating system requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Windows Vista® Home Basic/Home Premium/Business/Ultimate&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must meet minimum Windows Vista operating system requirements &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 class=&quot;cbMrgnBtmMD&quot;&gt;Windows® XP Home/Professional&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;300 MHz or faster processor&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;512 MB (1GB recommended) of RAM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;430 MB of available hard disk space&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CD-ROM or DVD-ROM drive for software distribution on media&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Super VGA (800 x 600) or higher resolution video adapter and monitor&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Windows® 8&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not ready for Windows 8&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Supported File Systems and Devices&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;FAT16, FAT16X, FAT32, FAT32X&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NTFS, GUID Partition Table (GPT)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dynamic Disks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Supported Hard Drives and Removable Media&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CDR/RW, DVD+-R/RW, Blu-Ray devices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;USB and FireWire® (IEEE 1394) devices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Iomega® Zip® and Jaz® drives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="longDesc">
            <value>&lt;p&gt;Protect your applications, settings, folders, and files with professional grade backup and recovery.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provides powerful control over full system and file backups&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Restores from system failures &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Backs up on schedules and events&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Saves recovery points to offsite locations including FTP &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="features">
            <value>&lt;div class=&quot;mod&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NEW! Cold Imaging&lt;/strong&gt; lets you back up files without installing Ghost.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NEW! Blu-ray Disc&lt;/strong&gt; allows you to back up large amounts of data to high-capacity Blu-ray Disc — up to 25 GB per disc (50 GB dual-layer).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NEW! Windows® 7 support&lt;/strong&gt; including support for Bitlocker™ provides enhanced data protection through drive encryption and integrity checking.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NEW! Symantec ThreatCon integration&lt;/strong&gt; leverages intelligence from Symantec’s industry-leading security research organization to automatically backup files whenever ThreatCon reaches a specified threat level.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Full system (disk image) backup&lt;/strong&gt; lets you easily back up everything on a hard drive or partition.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;File and folder backup&lt;/strong&gt; lets you back up only the files and folders you choose, rather than saving an entire drive.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;File backup search&lt;/strong&gt; finds and backs up only the types of files you choose, such as photos, MP3 files, and documents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incremental backup&lt;/strong&gt; copies only files that have changed for fewer, faster backups.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Customizable, event-based backup&lt;/strong&gt; triggers backups based on key events such as when you install a new program or when there are sudden increases in data storage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Offsite backup&lt;/strong&gt; copies recovery points to a FTP site for easier offsite backup management.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NAS backup&lt;/strong&gt; gives you the option of backing up your files to network-attached storage devices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advanced compression&lt;/strong&gt; automatically compresses files so you can store more files in less space.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advanced encryption&lt;/strong&gt; helps keep your sensitive documents safe from prying eyes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;System protection&lt;/strong&gt; lets you easily restore your system, applications and files even when you can’t restart the operating system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Google Desktop™ integration&lt;/strong&gt; makes data recovery even faster with searchable backup indexes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LightsOut Restore&lt;/strong&gt; lets you quickly restore your system without needing a bootable CD.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Remote management&lt;/strong&gt; lets you remotely control other Norton Ghost installations (12.0 and higher) on your local area network.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scheduled P2V&lt;/strong&gt; allows you to automatically create a virtual disk from your most recent backup.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Version support&lt;/strong&gt; lets you restore older disk images made with Ghost 10, 12 and 14.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Throttle control&lt;/strong&gt; allows backups to occur seamlessly in the background while you’re using your PC.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;File compression and password-encryption&lt;/strong&gt; ensure fast, efficient, secure backups.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;At-a-glance system status&lt;/strong&gt; displays all scheduled backups and the degree of backup protection for each computer drive, all in one view.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multiple storage options&lt;/strong&gt; let you back up to almost any media, including Blu-ray Disc®, CDR/RW and DVD+-R/RW drives, USB and FireWire® (IEEE 1394) devices, network drives, and Iomega® Zip® and Jaz® drives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="benefits">
            <value>&lt;div class=&quot;mod&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul id=&quot;accordianTab1&quot; class=&quot;listContent&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Automatically backup your files, photos and more&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Safeguards your photos, videos, music and other files with automatic backup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Takes periodic snapshots of your entire computer hard drive to be able to completely restore your computer system to a specific backup version in the case of hard drive failure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Automatically backs up when online threats raise an increased need to save the latest version of your system&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Convenient access for recovery&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lets you back up to and recover your files from a CD, DVD, Blu-ray Disc™, external drive or a networked attached storage (NAS) device&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provides easy recovery of your data files, or your entire hard drive or a mapped drive to a previous backup image&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Allows you to quickly restore your system without needing a bootable CD&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Thoughtful management&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;accordianContPad&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;default rightlist&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compresses disk images to store your backups in less space&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Encrypts your backups to keep your data safe from prying eyes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lets you remotely control other Norton Ghost installations (version 12.0 and higher) on your local area network&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</value>
        </attribute>
        <attribute key="shortDesc">
            <value language="en">Protect your applications, settings, folders, and files with professional grade backup and recovery.</value>
        </attribute>
    </attributes>
    <skus>
        <sku guid="56A64C55-146A-F12E-D24A-00F02CC8C58E">
            <code>NGH112TR</code>
            <shippable enabled="false"/>
            <digitalasset enabled="true">
                <file>software.exe</file>
                <downloadexpiry>0</downloadexpiry>
                <downloadlimit>0</downloadlimit>
            </digitalasset>
        </sku>
    </skus>
    <seo>
        <url>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </url>
        <title>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </title>
        <keywords>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </keywords>
        <description>
            <value language="fr"></value>
            <value language="en"></value>
        </description>
    </seo>
</product>
</products>
